Not at the table, son.
Come on.
Mmm-mmm.
Grace first.
You know better.
Father, we are gathered here
to share this food in your name.
Bless this food into our bodies, O Lord.
Bless our hearts
and all that we do, O Lord,
so that we may walk in your name...
Who will that be at this time?
I have no idea.
No.
♪ Three and thirty years ♪
♪ I tried ♪
♪ To forget ♪
♪ All the tears I cried ♪
Leave my family alone.
Theodore.
It's okay.
♪ Then one who knew me long ago... ♪
Leave them out of this.
Your quarrel is with me.
Let's go outside, take a walk,
and handle our business.
- Please.
- No.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Please, I'm begging you.
No!
No! No! No! No!
No! No! No!
No! No! Please!
No!
No! No, no, no, no, no! No!
Father Esparza?
I'm here for confession...
and the collection.
You know what happens
when you're late with my coins.
What possesses a man
to paint a scorpion on his hand?
Excuse me?
A snake,
I understand that.
The Garden of Eden, the Bible, etcetera.
But a scorpion?
Well, that puzzles me.
Who are you?
Just a man.
Here to kill the Scorpion.
Jesus Cortez.
Those were, uh, different times.
Whatever happened between you and I
must have been a long, long time ago.
No.
Please.
I...
I'm sorry.
Is it over?
This is a wanted man.
Turn his body in,
you'll get $5,000 for your church.
Why aren't you
taking him in yourself?
I'm worth ten.
♪ Avalon be damned ♪
♪ Venture foreign lands ♪
♪ I laid my sword in the sand ♪
♪ I've made my peace with man ♪
♪ They lay a violent feast ♪
♪ As far as my eyes can see ♪
♪ I seek a golden fleece ♪
♪ One day you'll make your peace ♪
♪ So don't tempt my hand ♪
♪ I'm just a man ♪
♪ A deadly scene, a weathered being ♪
♪ Men must cry where soldiers lie ♪
♪ On threatened land
My guns go bang ♪
♪ I can make the guns go bang ♪
♪ I make all the guns go bang ♪
♪ Dot Seventeen with the switch
It'll change you ♪
♪ Mama always said you was an angel ♪
♪ Papa got ghost
But these doors he never came through ♪
♪ He got ghost
But those walls he never came through ♪
♪ Stain glass windows in the church
I hope you stain proof ♪
♪ 'Cause when the tides change
I'm tryna stain you ♪
♪ Plotting for revenge
Dig your grave too ♪
♪ Whatever you want engraved
What your tombstone will say too ♪
♪ Crosses on the head of an angel ♪
♪ Sins of the father darken the doorstep
I became you ♪
♪ Faithful till the end ♪
♪ Bullets with your names drew
Cock back, aim, shoot, bang ♪
♪ Fragile life
A reflection of the past we leave behind ♪
♪ For sake of something new ♪
♪ Fractured smile, open windows
To the wounds we try to hide ♪
♪ Engraved in shadowed rooms ♪
♪ Bird in flight ♪
Yeah!
♪ Upon my return ♪
♪ See a changed soul ♪
♪ That road was far ♪
♪ And way too long ♪
♪ They'll run from me ♪
♪ As they ran from you ♪
♪ That fear in me ♪
♪ Is in a distant... ♪
♪ View ♪
It's the Nat Love Gang!
Stop firing! Stop firing!
It's one man! We got him pinned!
Wait for his head to show,
then blow the naps off that motherfucker.
Be patient.
I hear patience is a virtue.
But I ain't never been able to wait
to see if the motherfucker true.
- Jim Beckwourth.
- Brothers Grime.
It's Grimes with an "S,"
you egotistical piece of shit.
I remember a time
y'all hoods used to be crimson.
Known as the Crimson Hood Gang.
Them motherfuckers pink now.
You know, Mama used to say, "Jim is
such a sweet boy." You know what I said?
"Mama, fuck Jim!
Look what he did to my fucking eye!"
- I am sweet.
- You're not sweet.
- I'm sweet.
- You're not.
- Bitch, I'm sweet.
- You know what?
I'd rather be dead
than hear this motherfucker keep talking.
Whoo.
Much obliged, motherfuckers.
What the hell is that shit,
playing quick-draw games
when my ass is getting shot at?
Hey, hey.
You got your lucky coin, don't you?
Grow up, Jim.
This is real grown-men shit. We can die.
But we not gonna die.
'Cause I'm lightnin'
with the blam-blams. Admit it.
You know, you might could be,
but I hearsay there's a quick draw
more lightnin' than you,
go by the name of Cherokee Bill.
"Cherokee Bill."
You hearsay.
You don't see-say.
So I say fuck Cherokee Bill.
You know, rather than complaining,
you should be applauding my performance.
The only words that should be
coming out your Black-ass lips...
- "Black-ass lips"?
- ...should be...
- ...gracias.
- That was smooth.
- I know.
- Black lips are beautiful lips.
- Would you stop reaching, negro?
- God damn.
You just killed my brother.
Your half-brother, calm down.
Look like your day going a little bad.
Better than you sons of bitches
when you find out
whose money you done fucked with.
Correction. Who you done fucked with.
Y'all rob banks. We rob y'all.
And ain't a negro from here to Africa
gonna know we even exist.
You think I'm talking about a bank?
♪ I don't know ♪
♪ Where they go-oh-oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ Where are the children of men? ♪
♪ Questions that we did not know ♪
♪ Did not know ♪
♪ When will we see them again? ♪
♪ Questions that we did not know ♪
♪ Did not know ♪
♪ For queens and kings
And shining things ♪
♪ They gave our souls ♪
♪ But they soon learned
That freedom's better than gold ♪
♪ Oh, inna the days of old ♪
♪ Inna the days of old ♪
♪ These are the tales untold ♪
Evening, gent. Kindly check your weapon
and enjoy the festivities.
This is Stagecoach Mary's place
and ain't no guns allowed?
'Cept for Mary's, naturally.
Naturally.
Naturally, she put a fresh-faced pup
like yourself here to see to it.
Oh, I got to see
to a lot of things, Mr. Love.
People see me and they don't feel
too intimidated by what they see. See?
We familiar?
No, but you right famous
around these parts.
Folks say you once cut down
three men with one bullet.
Now, I ain't met a man
who can do that yet. Excuse me.
Evening, gents. Kindly check your weapons
and enjoy your evening.
I'd sooner check my right arm, boy.
Then you can head on over
to Jourdon Anderson's.
You can hold your weapon
and drink over there.
We drinking here, you puny little fuck.
Hey!
Some folk tend to feel a way, regardless.
Get 'em over to Doc Brown's.
Take they guns to the sheriff.
They can get 'em back
when they leave town.
What they call you?
They call me Cuffee.
This why I'm here!
Don't hurt nobody!
- ♪ One! ♪
- ♪ Get that horse and his wagon ♪
- ♪ Two! ♪
- ♪ Get that man and his rifle ♪
- ♪ Three! ♪
- ♪ Get that priest and his Bible ♪
- ♪ Four! ♪
- ♪ For them that's dead on arrival ♪
- ♪ Five! ♪
- ♪ Them that pray see heaven ♪
- ♪ Six! ♪
- ♪ Them that don't see the devil ♪
- ♪ Seven! ♪
- ♪ Separate but equal ♪
- ♪ Eight! ♪
- ♪ Say them that slaved my people ♪
- ♪ Nine! ♪
- ♪ So break them chains and shackles ♪
♪ Ten! ♪
Come again.
- ♪ One! ♪
- ♪ Get that horse and its wagon ♪
- ♪ Two! ♪
- ♪ Get that man and his rifle ♪
- ♪ Three! ♪
- ♪ Get that priest and his Bible ♪
- ♪ Four! ♪
- ♪ For them that's dead on arrival ♪
- ♪ Five! ♪
- ♪ Them that pray see heaven ♪
- ♪ Six! ♪
- ♪ Them that don't see the devil ♪
- ♪ Seven! ♪
- ♪ Separate but equal ♪
- ♪ Eight! ♪
- ♪ Say them that slaved my people ♪
- ♪ Nine! ♪
- ♪ So break them chains and shackles ♪
♪ Ten! ♪
Not again.
You still ain't talking to me?
Get out.
What?
I said leave.
What was that kiss for, then?
To remind you of what it was.
That's to remind you of what it is.
Excuse me.
Cuff, clean this man up.
- Oh, yes, ma'am.
- Thank you.
Second floor. Third room on the left.
Mary.
The only thing I need to hear
coming out your mouth is "Goodbye, Mary."
The one thing
you'll never hear me say again.
Till the next time you hear tell
of the whereabouts
of some man that done you dirt.
Ain't none of them left.
So you found the Scorpion?
Mary, the only thing that mean anything
to me in this world now
is you.
And what about the Nat Love Gang?
Ain't been much of a gang since you left.
Just me, Jim, Bill.
Next time they come around, I'll sort it.
Mmm.
You know, I can almost believe that.
Almost, 'cause you didn't get
the last one, did you?
You can say his name, Mary.
What about Rufus Buck?
Rufus in Yuma
for the rest of his natural life.
For a man like him,
that's worse than death.
As long as that man draw breath,
your spirit is gonna be cursed
and wild as it ever was.
Hmm.
I made things,
I built things,
and I ain't gonna risk all that
just because you decide
to come trottin' back.
- "Trottin'"?
- Yeah.
- Okay, well.
- Mmm-hmm.
I guess I came to the wrong saloon
'cause I ain't talking
to the Mary Fields I thought I knew.
- Yep. Things have changed.
- I see that.
Mmm-hmm.
'Cause that Mary...
That Mary...
...don't shy away from nothin'.
What was it the Apache called you?
Wolf Lady?
No. That's some bullshit
Pickett used to say.
That's bullshit Pickett used to say.
- Apache called me Coyote Woman.
- Hmm.
Yeah, Wolf Lady more like it.
My hat.
There.
I'm coming in.
Now, Wolf Lady,
don't blow the head off my neck.
- Nat.
- Pickett.
You got the worst timing
in the history of timing.
Oh, y'all was makin' sex?
I apologize.
But what I got to show you can't wait.
Well, well, well.
If it ain't the debonair dipshit himself.
Whoa, easy, Nat.
Listen to what the man got to say first.
So he can tell me
the same stories he been tellin' you?
Why the fuck would I lie?
Rufus Buck is behind bars
for the rest of his life.
- He gettin' out.
- How?
Damned if I know.
I just know it's so.
All the gangs are gettin' set
to ride for him again.
Half that take was his.
And you fools took his money.
You think Rufus Buck
was gonna let you keep half that money,
and you callin' me a fool?
I guess I am.
On your feet.
Exhale.
Now get out of here.
Leave.
What you doin'? We coulda killed
the last of the Crimson Hoods.
It's called the Crimson Hood Gang.
You think that's the last one?
Yeah.
I woulda bet my left six-shooter
he was about to kill that boy.
If that man telling the truth,
Nat just did him a whole lot worse.
♪ Whoa, seen! Here I come! ♪
♪ Here I come! ♪
What the hell
are you doin' out here?
That ain't no way to board a train,
you damn stupid ni...
You know, he might coulda said nincompoop.
We ain't no nincompoop.
If they say something
that even start with "N,"
they gonna meet the same fate.
Let 'em see your faces.
All right, stay calm, everybody.
Don't... Hey, don't touch nothin'.
My name is Cherokee Bill.
Now let it be known
that I don't particularly enjoy violence.
That being said,
you are currently in the company
of extremely violent individuals.
Try some of that.
Ugh. Shit.
So, don't do no stupid shit. All right?
Get off this train now,
you motherless scum.
You must be the hero.
Great Spirit, why is there always one?
You're rude.
I might actually enjoy
inflicting violence on you.
But who knows?
Maybe you'll win.
Let's see.
See my point?
Now, step aside so that we may conclude
our business here without further ado.
All right, everybody...
Stop right there.
No.
I said stop.
Put the weapon down, boy.
Or we kill everybody on this train.
I said put the gun down.
It's okay.
Are there any more soldiers on that car?
There are.
Exactly how many?
Thirty.
Ten!
See, that's all you had to say.
Open the door.
I said open the damn door.
Here we are.
My dear battalion.
I imagine you have
all your artillery aimed at the door.
I'd like to inform you
that in front of that door
lies one of your very own troops.
Any bullets coming through that door
will hit him first, okay?
State your name, criminal.
Oh, I'm not a criminal, sir, um,
but my name is Cherokee Bill.
What's your name?
My name is Officiant of the Goddamn Law.
You let that soldier go immediately.
Leave this train now
and no one will be hurt.
Oh, that sounds like fear talking,
Mr. Officiant of the Goddamn Law.
And we done already hurt a couple people.
You're just going to let us
get away Dred Scott free?
State your purpose, bastard.
Also, I'm not a bastard.
But you've got something we want.
We've got a soldier that you want.
Now, I suggest we make a peaceful trade
and everybody lives to see another day.
- Sound dandy?
- Just let the boy go.
Jake!
I'm okay, Pa!
That's just a flesh wound, sir.
You got ten seconds to put your guns down
and open up this damn door,
or your little kin here shall perish.
Harm him further and I will kill every
last one of you godless sons of bitches.
Goddamn, Trudy.
You know I like my countdowns.
My apologies, sir.
My friend here doesn't like arithmetic.
Be that as it may, seven seconds.
Six.
- Lay down your rifles.
- Five.
I said lay them down.
Four.
Three.
Well, all right. Thank you kindly.
Go ahead and walk, boy.
Keep walkin'. Just keep moving.
No one do anything stupid.
Just walk like you been taught.
Left, right, left. Left, right, left.
Left, right, left.
♪ Skip to the Lou, my darlin' ♪
- Open it.
- I can't.
The key is back in Yuma. And the next...
One more time.
You will be hounded
to the ends of the earth for this.
I don't like long distances,
Lieutenant General Abbott.
Ever cross your mind
why you was given the task
of transporting a lone outlaw
from one prison to another?
Full pardon for Mr. Buck
and all his associates for all misdeeds.
Signed General George Pryce.
What's this about?
Well, he came to us with a proposition.
Kill a particular
Officiant of the Goddamn Law.
A man so crooked that even the government
is embarrassed by his misdeeds.
Apparently, you and your men
wiped out an entire town,
women and children included,
to steal silver.
- Now, that's some unscrupulous shit.
- Unscrupulous shit.
Please. I'll dis...
Shh.
No!
Pa! No, no, no, no, no.
Pa.
No.
Who here can drive a train?
I said...
Everybody but him.
♪ Whoa, seen! Here I come! ♪
♪ I'm broad ♪
♪ I'm broader than Broadway ♪
Evening, sir. Check your weapon with me
and enjoy what's left of the night.
Oh, no need to show me that star.
I know who you is.
In here, though, I be the sheriff,
and that make Ms. Mary the marshal.
And the marshal say,
"Don't nobody come in here gunned up,
or they might could get gunned down."
My badge begs to differ.
Check your gun-belt.
Excuse me.
So how you plan on taking me in, Marshal?
Staring me to death?
How about just death?
Just a pipe.
You mind?
Never known you to touch it.
Only after I kill a man.
Or before.
I was on the trail
of the Crimson Hood Gang
on account of a bank robbery
in Kansas City.
Turned out somebody got to 'em before me.
You know I don't rob banks, Marshal.
But you rob them that do,
which is all the same to me.
- Texas.
- What?
I was in Texas
at the time of that robbery.
How you know when it took place?
Whenever any bank robbery took place,
I was in Texas.
Unless, of course,
the robbery took place in Texas.
Way I hear it, some of them boys
with the Crimson Hoods
are part of a new Rufus Buck Gang, Nat.
Rufus in Yuma.
He out. But you knew that already,
didn't you?
Why you sitting here monologuing,
drinking up my whiskey,
when you should be out
rounding up your little deputies?
'Cause he been pardoned, Nat.
Rufus Buck been absolved
of his countless depredations.
Seeing as I've been scouring the terrain
looking for bank robbers and such,
that particular piece of news
failed to reach me.
What they sayin'?
Something about guns, killin'.
Why you let that kid take my gun?
What kinda stupid rule is that?
- Should be four guns pointing at...
- Shut up, Pickett.
You shoot, he dead.
You miss,
all y'all die.
You, come here.
Take these cuffs. Cuff this man.
Or I put three in his chest right now,
lessen the trouble.
Go on.
Tell this young buck to back up.
Easy, Jim.
Everybody in here know who I am.
I'm taking Nat Love
to Fort Smith to be tried.
Anybody try to follow me,
y'all know what I do.
Come on.
Y'all enjoy the rest of the evening.
♪ Well, now ♪
♪ Whoa-oh, well ♪
♪ The promise land ♪
♪ Going to the promise land ♪
♪ Yes, the promise land ♪
♪ Oh gosh now ♪
♪ To the promise land ♪
♪ Make a step down to Wasmara ♪
♪ Then we stopped in Addis Ababa ♪
♪ Made our way to Shashamane land ♪
♪ Riding on the king's highway ♪
♪ To the promise land ♪
♪ Going to the promise land ♪
♪ Oh gosh ♪
♪ To the promise land ♪
♪ Yeah, the promise land ♪
Rufus.
Cherokee Bill, Ms. Smith,
top of the morning to you both.
Mr. Buck, glad to have you
back in Redwood, sir.
Any word on the take
from the Kansas City bank?
The Crimson Hoods took it for $25,000.
But they were ambushed
before they got here.
Everybody knows
it's suicide to take from us.
Someone obviously disagrees.
Goddamn it. That just put us
right back where we started.
How we supposed to build a Mecca
without any bricks?
We gonna have to
take it out of our own bank.
We don't have
that type of money, Trudy.
We only got a few pennies over $2,500.
What did he say?
- 2,500...
- I heard you.
- Wiley.
- Yeah.
Sure is hot, ain't it?
What's up, little man?
- You wanna see something?
- Yeah.
Watch this now.
Don't take your eyes off it.
Oh, it's still there!
Rufus Buck.
Look at you.
Relic of yesteryear with nothin'.
And you think you can roll into my town
and take what belong to me?
Who the fuck you think I am, huh?
Ain't nobody scared of you
and ain't nobody runnin'.
I'm a sinister motherfucker too.
One click of my finger and you disappear.
So I suggest you leave...
before I finish my steak.
And if you even think about sticking...
Come in.
What is it, Carson?
Sheriff, Mr. Buck wants
to see you out front.
Tell that man
I ain't got nothing to say to him.
It wasn't a request.
Wiley Escoe.
Rufus.
You wanna sell this town
while I rot in prison?
The world you knew is gone.
There's a flood comin'.
Do you think
you can hold onto this place when it hit?
At least I know enough
to get mine and get out.
Kill me...
and you'll have nothing.
You know, a man like you
will have us all subservient
till the end of our days
so's long as you can buy yourself a house,
a badge,
and them goddamn gold teeth.
You want to do this here?
There you go.
That's what you want, right?
That's what you came here for?
I won't disappoint you. Come on.
That's what you want. Want some more?
You want some more, right?
You want some more?
Come here, motherfucker.
Here you go.
Oh shit. I done hit gold.
Hey, boy. Come here.
Come, get that gold. Get that gold.
All right. Tell your mama
you rich now! Go ahead!
Now,
I ain't gonna kill you, Wiley.
You and I were friends once.
But know this.
Redwood will never be yours, never.
Never.
Matter of fact,
you ain't welcome here no more.
Now...
I want you to vacate immediately
or die where you lay.
Say what?
That's right.
♪ Going home to my Lord ♪
♪ I'm going home ♪
♪ I'm going home now to my Lord ♪
♪ I'm going home to my Lord ♪
♪ I'm going home to my Lord ♪
♪ I'm going home now to my Lord ♪
You coulda taken these off a while back.
Yep.
Tell me something.
How you know Rufus will be in Redwood?
He's taking that money
from them Crimson Hoods.
That's where he'll be.
Now you teaming up
with a marshal to bring him in.
I ain't bringing him in.
I'm bringing him down.
And we ain't teaming up, old man.
Your life's expendable, Marshal.
My gang's ain't.
Shit, since we're out here,
I oughta tell you...
I was fixin' to kill you...
when you and your fellas brought in Rufus.
A lot of men be fixin', son.
They always seem to die
before they get the job done.
Just for the record...
I took Rufus in alone.
Mary.
I figured you'd be halfway
to Fort Smith by now.
You can put that gun down, Marshal.
This ain't a ambush.
You, on the other hand,
might wanna keep yours handy.
Do you think I'm stupid enough
to fall for that bullshit
y'all pulled in my saloon?
I don't want you mixed up in this no more.
Then you shoulda told me so.
I must confess
to some raw feelings myself.
This ain't no road
to ask a friend to travel.
Now you take that money
we took off them Crimson Hoods
and you buy that ranch
you always blabbing about. Hmm?
That's mighty generous of you,
but that ain't how this gang work.
Take stays in the usual place, ready
to be shared three ways when we come back.
Ain't no coming back from this.
Now get out of here.
All of you. This ain't your fight.
You take on the Devil himself, you gonna
need more than you and the marshal.
I seen the Devil,
and Rufus Buck ain't him.
Devil's white.
You got a reason you wanna die, Jim?
Outside of you saving me from this?
Besides, Monroe said
Cherokee Bill run with Rufus.
Every time I speak on my speed,
a motherfucker wanna pull
Cherokee Bill out they ass.
I'ma put a end to that argument
once and for all.
Like they say in the Book of Clarence,
"No man out-speed me."
Out-speed ain't a word,
and Clarence ain't no book.
I'm hopin' Cherokee put a bullet
in your ass just to shut you up.
- Hey.
- You left these on my wall, Mr. Love.
Figured we going after villains,
you'll need 'em.
Obliged.
What y'all waiting around for?
You think destiny is comin' to you?
Hyup! Go!
Yeah. I know.
Go ahead.
♪ Wahala they go
Wahala they come ♪
♪ Wahala they ride
Wahala they run ♪
♪ Wahala they sing ♪
♪ Wahala they go
Wahala they come ♪
♪ Wahala they ride
Wahala they run ♪
♪ Wahala they sing
Wahala they call ♪
♪ Wahala they fly
Wahala they fall ♪
♪ Wahala they go
Wahala they come ♪
♪ Wahala they ride
Wahala they run ♪
How do I look?
All right.
Everybody out there?
Just about.
How could you do it?
Leave all of this to Wiley?
If you were runnin' Redwood,
who woulda kept the operation goin'?
Who else woulda kept
all them gangs in line?
Look, I know that Wiley got his ways,
but he was loyal once.
Loyalty is a virtue, Rufus.
Till it ain't.
You loyal to me?
See these folk here?
Either they can't see it
or they don't want to.
But I believe in what you're doing.
This place can be
the promised land for us.
And as long as that so, ain't nothing
I won't do to see it through.
You tell them.
Citizens of Redwood.
A new day is dawning.
As by now you have doubtless learned,
the territory will officially
open up for settlement.
Now they say everything we own
is gonna stay our own.
But you know as well as I do
how much that's worth.
See, your land,
your businesses, your homes
has all been promised
to the highest bidders
by your one-time sheriff, Wiley Escoe.
Now, Mr. Buck can prevent this
from happening.
But in order for us to do that,
it's necessary that we levy a tax.
At what cost to us?
- $50,000.
- Ooh.
You could scrape every penny
from every living soul in this town,
and it wouldn't come near to that.
You got us between a rock
and a hard place.
How long you been alive in this country?
A rock and a hard place
is what we call Monday.
I've heard of Rufus Buck.
How bad a man he is.
But he got himself
thrown in jail once before,
and I reckon
he'll be back there again soon enough.
When he is,
maybe I'll come back to this town.
'Cause I ain't paying shit.
You think I made Redwood for myself?
To what end?
Redwood ain't a hiding place,
'cause I don't hide.
It ain't a dream.
I don't dream.
You know what it is?
It's an example.
It's an example...
for others to follow.
And you...
you are an enemy of progress.
Please. Please.
- I got a family.
- What's your name?
James.
Rest in peace, James.
Now, how much?
How much can be gathered?
Ten thousand.
Maybe 15,
if every last cent can be squeezed.
Mmm-hmm.
Ain't nobody leave town
until we collect it all.
And if you fail to comply,
you and everything you love will burn.
I ain't got nothin' to rob.
But I got somebody to shoot.
Step down.
Wiley Escoe.
Bass Reeves.
Fuck.
Redwood crawling with gunmen.
Rufus came with 12 and took six of mine.
Who knows how many he got by now.
I don't believe a thing this man sayin'.
He a scout.
I say we kill him.
And we take the rest of them teeth.
You ever shot a sheriff, boy?
A mayor?
Little harder than shootin' regular folk.
And I'm both.
You both alive and dead
'cause Rufus don't like loose ends.
Law don't find a man like Rufus Buck
unless you got inside information.
Ain't that right, Wiley?
If I had my way, you'd be right up
under the jail next to Rufus.
But you cut yourself a deal,
wound up wearing a badge instead.
You got your reasons
you want Rufus gone, and I got mine.
Ain't the enemy of my enemy my friend?
Rufus tryin' to save Redwood.
But for that, he need money.
And that's one thing he ain't have.
All right, look here.
You made a deal with the Devil.
Now he come to collect.
You rest up,
but be gone before sunup.
Or it's gonna go from bad to badder.
You hear?
Ooh.
Marshal.
Marshal. Marshal.
All them tricks'll get you killed, son.
Listen, Marshal.
I'm faster than any weapon.
You can trust in that.
I seen faster.
All right. Where?
In the mirror.
Negro said, "In the mirror."
I'm so... I'm sorry.
I rather ride into a gun battle
on a dark horse over a golden stallion.
- Fuck that mean?
- Shiny shit get shot.
You gonna shoot me?
What you think about that, lawman?
I think y'all gonna die.
♪ And away with the wind ♪
♪ She goes ♪
♪ As her garden grows ♪
♪ Hold those flowers close ♪
♪ For away with the wind ♪
♪ She goes ♪
I'll be back with information by sunup.
Information from where?
Redwood.
You know we can't trust Wiley's word.
Someone's got to get the lay of the land
before we make our next move.
Yeah, Mary, but that somebody
ain't got to be you.
Every gunhand
in the territory's gonna recognize you
the second you hop off your horse.
Same with Bill and Beckwourth.
In case you forgot,
your face more famous than all of ours
put together, Stagecoach Mary.
Got it up on advertisements
for that saloon of yours
from here to Texas.
Which is why I can
ride into town in plain sight.
Everybody knows I'm buying saloons.
Rufus need money. I'ma make him an offer
on Trudy Smith's place...
Mary, what in my character
makes you think I'll allow that?
I'm not asking for your permission.
All right.
Then I... I guess
I'll just be asking you for yours.
Since you'll never let
a man give you away,
I just have to ask you direct.
That's the ring my father gave my mother.
I was gonna give it to you
back in Douglas.
But you didn't.
I am now.
I used to hate feeling helpless over you.
Those days are over now.
Mary...
When the dust settles,
we gonna go our separate ways, for good.
But not till the dust settles.
I'm here till then.
See you sunup.
♪ Woman cry, give life ♪
♪ Mother Mary and baby
The burden she carries all time ♪
♪ Woman cry gives us life ♪
♪ And she begs he forgives us
The sin and the sinners all time ♪
Whoa.
Are you a resident of Redwood, ma'am?
You don't own a gun
confident enough to ask where I reside.
Well, this gun say
answer the damn question.
Well, this gun don't talk.
Stagecoach Mary.
Ghastly Gertrude Smith.
I prefer Treacherous Trudy myself,
but I'll take it.
What brings you to my town?
I heard Rufus Buck was back.
News travels fast.
I have an offer he might wanna hear about.
Well, any offer you got,
you can make it to me.
I don't do business with the help.
Give me that shit.
Lead the way, Treacherous Trudy.
♪ Monday's child is ever smiling ♪
♪ Tuesday's child will play inside ♪
♪ Wednesday comes with a gun ♪
♪ Thursday's tears have just begun ♪
♪ Friday's ships are filled with crying ♪
♪ Monday seems so far away now ♪
♪ Tuesday was not bad at all ♪
♪ Wednesday came with a flame ♪
♪ Thursday never be the same ♪
♪ Friday's ships are not returning ♪
♪ Monday's child is torn asunder ♪
♪ Tuesday's child is thrown in chains ♪
♪ Wednesday's child used to smile ♪
♪ Thursday's tears are now a Nile ♪
♪ Friday's child is ever burning ♪
Speak your piece.
I assume you know who I am.
I assume you know who I used to run with.
Those days are over for me anyhow,
but I didn't get to be
Stagecoach Mary Fields
without having my ears to the ground
and my ears tell me you just lost
25 thou that was coming your way.
I hope your proposal
rivals your nerve...
Allow me the latitude of completion.
My saloon in Douglas is boomin'.
Bought me another one in the Elks,
and I got a restaurant in Cascade too.
For the sum of all that,
I could take this one off your hands.
The mere mention of my name
brings forth good business
to any establishment attached, whereas,
with all due respect,
but the name Rufus Buck instils fear.
We know who you are.
You walkin' into my town
with that proposal is risky.
The kind of risk a woman such as yourself
wouldn't tie herself to
unless there was
a whole lot more at stake.
See, I don't believe in coincidence,
like you just gonna walk in here
right after the Crimson Hoods
get ambushed with my money.
What are you thinking?
Oops.
You must have forgot
whose name is on the door.
Another round.
We havin' a party, y'all. Come on.
All right, Mary.
All right.
So you still sayin'
you don't know nothin' about that money
and you done come here alone?
That's right.
You done rode all the way over here
to get yourself killed.
And for what?
For love?
Love is the only thing worth dying for.
But you wouldn't know anything about that.
You know,
I had a sister named Mary.
She was pretty, strong-willed, like you.
She died of polio when I was 11.
Always was in pain,
but she'd never let me see her cry.
Mmm.
There's this girl called Hope lived by us.
Big fat kid,
always picking on the smaller kids.
Obviously out of jealousy.
But she ain't never fuck with me though.
She hated Mary with a passion,
always teasing her
about how thin and frail she was.
Then one day,
Hope walkin' by our house,
apple in one hand, blade in the other.
She decided to throw the apple
across the street at Mary,
and it hit my sister in the head
and knocked her out of balance.
She fell down the steps.
Broke her ankle.
And now that...
that was the first and only time
I physically seen my sister cry.
And there was Hope standing there
laughin' her ugly fuckin' face off.
My daddy...
he got home,
he took off his belt, and he beat me
for not protecting my sister.
He lashed me
until my whole body went numb.
Then
he went to Hope house
to do the same thing to her.
When he got there, he saw her whole family
standin' on the side of the house,
all of 'em screamin' and cryin',
and there was Hope...
lyin' on the floor in a pool of blood.
Somebody had slit her throat.
Killed her with her own knife.
Daddy was speechless.
He ain't said a word to me
when he came home.
The next day,
he sent me to live with my grandparents.
And then the next time I seen my sister,
she was laying in a coffin.
Disease had killed her.
I'm sorry your sister had to suffer.
I admire her bravery.
But you get no words from me.
You know,
I actually admire your bravery.
But I'm afraid the outcome
is still the outcome.
Hope
must die.
But not yet.
Leave her out here in the street
so everybody can see her.
No one come to collect her 'fore sunup,
put a bullet in her head.
Yes, ma'am.
Looks like we don't
have to wait that long.
Whoever die first, right?
- Whoever die first.
- Mmm-hmm.
Get her up.
"Whoever die first"?
Now, what kind of dumbass saying is that?
You two trying to get shot out here?
Nat Love. How predictable.
You predict my friend Bill Pickett
aiming at your bowler cap?
You'll be dead
before your boys get their aim.
And you die right after.
But your boss won't see
one red cent of that money.
My boss?
Where is he?
Where is who?
Marshal.
I'm speakin' English, yeah?
- Sound like English to me.
- Mmm-hmm.
Where's Rufus Buck?
Oh.
Ooh-hoo.
Bass.
Trudy.
If I'd known you were switchin' sides,
I'da asked you to come join us.
You here for your damsel in distress?
You don't look hard of hearing.
So I'ma ask you again.
Where's Rufus Buck?
Well, clearly, you don't know me.
Tell your men to go,
but you stay,
and maybe your damsel
will live a little longer.
Marshal.
Oh.
You're pretty though.
- Ah, take her ass back in there.
- Yes, ma'am.
Gonna get me a drink.
Hey.
That the quick draw
I hear tell about, Cherokee Bill?
I hear you so fast
that your opponents ain't got time to draw
before you put two in they back.
No, that ain't me.
I'm the Cherokee Bill that shoots men
in the mouth that talk too much.
I'll make it easy for you, then.
You draw first.
That what you think this is?
"Who the quickest draw in the West?"
All comes down
to who fast and who ain't, right?
No, it all comes down
to who's alive and who's dead.
Trudy, I'm gonna get me
something to drink.
Good night.
Hey, hey, drink, my ass, man.
- I practiced that standoff all night.
- Jim.
- You're not about to walk away.
- Get out of here.
- No, nobody...
- Get out of here, Jim.
- That chicken...
- It ain't the time.
Okay. Okay.
March, boy.
- I said march!
- March.
Hup, two, three, four.
That's enough.
They beat you bad?
I'ma kill 'em all.
You familiar with Napoleon?
He said, "I am driven towards an end
that I do not know."
"As I reach it,
as I shall become unnecessary,
an atom shall suffice to shatter me."
"Until then, all forces of humankind
can do nothing to stop me."
That's a man who knew exactly who he was.
Most importantly,
he knew that
his time would come to an end.
Cut him down.
You know why...
I gave you that scar?
So I'd remember you.
No.
No, I gave you that scar so I can know
your face when you come back to me.
Nat Love,
the outlaw who robs outlaws,
the angel of death who hunts down those
who trespass against him with no mercy.
I know who you are.
And I see the line that you won't cross.
See, I know what's on the other side.
Apologize for the beating.
It was more of an indication
for what Ms. Fields might see
if we fail to come to terms.
What terms?
You will return the money
you stole from me by Friday noon.
Not a moment later.
And you will add $10,000 on top of that.
We'll call that interest.
Somethin' funny?
Ooh, shit, how...
how you reckon I'ma get that?
You're gonna rob a bank.
Nat Love is gonna rob a bank.
In the meantime, here's a little token
of my appreciation in advance.
Go ahead, open it.
I expect my money on Friday.
All of it.
You know I can't let you do that.
If that money ain't in Rufus' hands
in three days, Mary'll die.
What bank
we talking about anyway?
Maysville.
Maysville?
That's a white town.
Yeah, which is why
they gonna have $10,000 in their bank.
It's crazy.
My emotions
are all types of confused.
I mean, Pickett, I agree. That's crazy.
But, Nat, I also agree with you
telling the marshal
that we gonna do that shit anyways.
That's some true outlaw shit.
- We outlaws, ain't we?
- Ain't no "we," Jim.
Not after that shit you pulled in town
nearly got us all killed.
I had that.
Fetch that money
you took from the Crimson Hoods.
Pickett, kid, you comin' with me.
If Rufus Buck want that bank took,
why don't he send his own men?
This way he clean, see?
I gotta go in barefaced as day,
a freshly minted bank robber, face up
on wanted posters all over the territory.
They'll be on you like flies on shit
before you open the door.
Yep.
I said I had to be recognized.
Go ahead.
Hell no.
For Mary.
Whoo! Hoo!
Close shave.
Close fucking shave!
I thought I was
falling for a fella for a little bit.
That's why I didn't say nothing.
Well, I ain't the only one. I can't...
I can't... It wasn't just me.
It wasn't just me.
It was just you, Jim.
♪ Follow, follow
People they go they follow ♪
♪ People they know they copy
Go all up in my grotto ♪
♪ They see me like a genie
Try to keep me in a bottle ♪
♪ Petty, petty people
Keep them incommunicado ♪
♪ They tie you up with strings
They play niggas like pizzicato ♪
Giddup now.
Allow me.
What's your real name?
Cuffee my real name.
Name I was born with?
Cathay Williams.
You walk worse than you ride, Cathay.
Mr. Love, my momma always told me
to respect my elders,
so I'm not gonna say what I'm thinking.
That's all right. I can read your mind.
Then I'm sorry you had to hear that.
Go ahead.
Go ahead, honey.
Yes?
I'd like to make a withdrawal.
Ooh.
What...
You have to have an account, ma'am.
And, well, I'd recommend a bank
in Jericho or maybe Redwood for that.
Oh.
I'm not talking about
that kinda withdrawal.
I'm talk...
I'm talking about...
talking about that kind.
Hey, blue eyes.
You scared.
Your hand is shaking. You'll miss.
I won't.
Exhale.
Attaboy.
I ain't like my partner.
He don't wanna shoot nobody,
but all of a sudden, I'm of a mind to.
Now open the fuckin' gate.
Think I'm funny now?
What you lookin' at?
Get all the customers over there.
- Get 'em over there!
- Okay, okay.
- Everyone, please, this way quickly.
- You too. Move!
Times have changed, ain't they?
They say robbing banks is hard work.
That's a lie. Robbing banks is easy.
The hard part is doing it without killing.
So, what'll it be...
Mr. Manager?
Good man.
Come on. Let's go.
Come on. Giddyap. Go.
Come on, come on.
- Pleasure banking with you.
- Okay, sir.
Nat Love.
Don't even look like much.
Ain't what it look like.
It's what it can buy you.
Rufus won't let Mary go
once he gets that money.
Yeah, I know it.
He'll kill her,
let me go, so's I carry that hurt with me.
So what, we just went through
all that trouble for nothin'?
Now we got something he want.
And that's it?
Gonna have to be.
You can be all hasty
and shoot me now if you want,
or you can wait to see
what I brought with me first.
Ooh.
Rufus got stashes like this
all across these hills.
Enough for a small army.
Don't nobody take what I got coming to me.
Not even the Devil himself.
Rufus Buck is a man.
Y'all best reconcile yourselves
with that fact.
Man or devil,
this gonna be
Buck's last day amongst the living.
♪ Upon my return ♪
♪ See a changed soul ♪
- ♪ That road was far ♪
- ♪ And way too long ♪
- ♪ They'll run from me ♪
- ♪ As they ran from you ♪
- ♪ That fear in me ♪
♪ Is in a distant view ♪
♪ Is ♪
♪ In a distant ♪
♪ View ♪
Whoa there, whoa there. Whoa.
Afternoon.
I would ask you to run
go fetch your superior,
but that'd be like asking you
to run go fetch your daddy.
It could be anybody, right?
Hmm.
You know,
I'm willing to bet my right arm
I've got a higher body count than yours.
That'd be a bad bet, son.
I fancy that song or whatever it was
you was whistling there.
Go, Jerry. Go.
That our money?
Uh...
Walk with me.
Hey, just... just walk with me.
- Keep an eye on this, Angel.
- Mmm-hmm.
You know they call your boss
the Devil hisself?
Even the Devil needed money, right?
So being as how we are
in possession of that money...
let me dictate the terms of engagement.
What the fuck was that?
What the fuck was that, old man?
Is that the right arm or the left?
Oh man.
Well, now there's us...
and there's y'all.
Whoa.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
You get a hold of your feisty buddy here.
You got a little rowdy rascal.
- Mary.
- Yeah, we'll get to that.
- We gonna count this first.
- Now, Cherokee.
Or your boss gonna be
one quick draw and $35,000 short.
All right.
Unhitch this horse so's Mary can ride out.
- You always move so slow?
- You always talk so much?
Really?
In the back?
What you think, Beckwourth?
Nah, he wouldn't do that
'cause then I would have to put
a bullet in his cranium.
And we'll never know
who the fastest really is now, will we?
I gotta hand it to you, boy.
You do know how to make a grand entrance.
Shit, I didn't even rehearse that one.
You know, quick draw,
Nat Love is a dead man walking.
But you don't have to be.
Why don't you get on your horse,
get your shit,
and go back to
whatever it is you call home?
You know that's impossible.
Count down from five?
Five...
Four...
Three...
Why do they always have to count so slow?
Jim!
Blow that bitch, Bill!
♪ Do unto others ♪
♪ As you will have them do ♪
Kill her.
♪ Oh, that reaper, he gonna win ♪
♪ All them people that live in sin ♪
♪ Give that lady a ring of fire ♪
♪ You're dead in your blood ♪
♪ That's yo woman
Ain't no better love ♪
♪ All them people that live in sin ♪
Mary!
Push!
♪ There dat coffin you gonna lie, so ♪
Trudy's mine.
♪ Dead in your blood ♪
♪ That's yo woman
Ain't no better love ♪
We gonna play for you
our first tune tonight.
And the first tune is called...
O l'oun t'awa se n'yara. Je k'abere
Which means,
"Let's start what we have come
into the room to do."
Let's go.
♪ One, two, three! ♪
Son of a bitch!
Exhale, motherfucker.
Come on.
- Where'd they get you?
- Shoulder. Get down!
Matches.
You wanna smoke now?
Matches, Bass.
Okay.
Jump, motherfuckers.
Fuck it.
I always knew it was you
who gave me up.
God knew my heart.
Goodbye, old friend.
Rufus, I didn't have a choice...
I told that kid.
Them damn tricks...
Sorry, ladies.
- You all right, Cuffee?
- Just need to reload.
You look hurt, Mr. Pickett.
Ain't nothing but a flesh wound.
Maggie ain't ready for me today.
Huh?
What the fuck?
I'll be damned.
Pickett!
Now, why you got
that look on your face?
No. No, no, no, brother, no, no, no.
Stop that. Don't do that.
You had a choice.
You always got a choice.
Being scared will only
give you bad karma in the afterlife.
He didn't even have a chance,
you son of a bitch!
You gonna shoot me in the back too?
Or cheat the count?
♪ I lost my shadow in violent sin ♪
♪ Never knew the search would be within ♪
Beckwourth was faster.
♪ Drew a picture of my only desire ♪
♪ Take me back to Blackskin Mile ♪
♪ I thought my karma would be my fate ♪
♪ Never saw the sun
Until it was too late ♪
♪ And, oh ♪
♪ Drew my loneliness
Chasing every last high ♪
♪ Take me back to Blackskin Mile ♪
♪ I never met a madman's soul ♪
♪ That I didn't see reflections
Of that which I own ♪
♪ But I know
There's something better outside ♪
♪ So won't you
Take me back to Blackskin Mile? ♪
Look after my friend.
Nat.
Don't miss.
Pick up your guns.
I know what it is now.
It's the eyes.
Pick 'em up, I said.
Your father,
he was a good man?
He was.
And my mother was a good woman
before you cut 'em down.
Seems we had a different upbringing.
I don't care how you was raised.
Now pick up your guns and turn around.
I used to watch my father
beat my mother to a pulp
if she overcooked his food.
He cut her up real good
if she undercooked it too.
One day, I decided to intervene,
and he turned his wrath on me.
My father was not a good man.
Not a good man. He was an outlaw.
Robbin' banks...
He liked to drink.
My mother took a bottle
and cut him to protect me.
He lashed back at her,
and just like that, she was gone.
Then, like the coward he is,
he took everything we had and left,
leaving me with my...
my mother.
I was ten years old, you know...
about the same age you was...
when I gave you that scar.
I had to fend for myself,
but I became who I am,
just like you.
As I did, all I could ever think about is
wanting my father to pay for what he did.
I searched for him for years and years,
and I could never find him.
It's like he disappeared
off the face of the earth.
I ain't stop though. I kept looking...
until I did find him.
One day...
lo and behold,
there he was,
my father,
a new man.
He was clean now.
Sober.
Man of God.
Had a church.
He had a pretty little wife.
And he had a son,
about the age of ten years old,
whose eyes blazed like mine.
You're lyin'.
You're lyin'!
Killing our father was retribution, but...
My father!
My mother!
But it weren't enough.
Letting you live,
that was the true revenge.
Every sin you made, every bank you robbed,
everybody you killed.
I mean, look at you.
You everything he tried to run away from.
Buck.
Changed his name to "Love."
You a Buck.
You lyin'.
Just like me.
Just like him.
But you better.
You gonna surpass even me because...
I couldn't kill my brother.
Yet here you are about to kill yours.
It's time to take your revenge,
Nathaniel Buck.
Go on.
- Nathaniel Buck.
- No.
Take your revenge.
Nathaniel Buck.
Take your goddamn revenge!
You a Buck.
Nathaniel Buck.
Nathaniel...
♪ And upon my return ♪
♪ You'll see a changed soul ♪
♪ The road ♪
♪ Was far too long ♪
Is the Devil dead?
I don't know.
♪ They'll run from me ♪
♪ As they ran from you ♪
♪ The fear in me ♪
♪ Is in a distant view ♪
♪ And there ain't no turning around ♪
All right, fellas.
You sure the law gonna believe he's dead?
I'm the law, Ms. Mary.
If I say a man dead, he dead.
And you?
You sure this what you want?
I always kinda wanted to be
a deputy, sheriff, marshal person.
♪ Hold up your lighter and come ♪
♪ Flame inna de air, fire fi bun ♪
♪ Holla from the top of a mountain
And cry ♪
♪ Tell them
Say my love will never die ♪
What you lookin' at?
We got work to do, Mr. Love.
Hup.
Let's go.
♪ And when we get there, we shall sing ♪
♪ The harder they fall ♪
♪ Across the heaven
Love shall ring, ring, ring... ♪
All right.
♪ Where shall we walk?
Where shall we run and run? ♪
Where shall we run? ♪
♪ Over the mountain to the sun ♪
♪ On to the sun ♪
♪ And when we get there, we shall sing ♪
♪ And we shall sing ♪
♪ Across the heaven
Love will ring, ring, ring, ring ♪
♪ Hold up your lighter and come ♪
♪ Flame inna de air, fire fi bun ♪
♪ Holla from the top of a mountain
And cry ♪
♪ Tell 'em
Say my love will never die ♪
♪ Where do we go? ♪
♪ A long and winding road ♪
♪ The louder they roar ♪
♪ The harder that they fall ♪
- ♪ See fi de man with him bible and gun ♪
- ♪ See him deh ♪
♪ Badman no scarper nah run ♪
- ♪ See fi de woman afraid of no man ♪
- ♪ See she deh ♪
- ♪ Bad gyal no scarper nah run ♪
- ♪ Pam pam ♪
♪ Lick a shot
And every man wave your hand ♪
- ♪ Pam pam ♪
- ♪ All of de woman jussa rise and stand ♪
- ♪ Oh gosh ♪
- ♪ Bandolero dem a watch when we walk ♪
♪ Bad gyal no take bak no talk
When I say ♪
♪ Hold up your lighter and come ♪
♪ Flame inna de air, fire fi bun ♪
♪ Holla from the top of a mountain
And cry ♪
♪ Tell 'em
Say my love will never die ♪
♪ Where do we go? ♪
♪ A long and winding road ♪
♪ The louder they roar ♪
♪ The harder that they fall ♪
♪ Fire fi bun
Mister Man we have no time to play ♪
♪ You love a woman
Tell her night and day ♪
♪ Send dem come
Jah know me tell you right away ♪
♪ Me love you like me love me waistline ♪
♪ Dress pretty pretty
Still me a walk nitty gritty ♪
♪ Round up de woman committee
And ride fi him city ♪
♪ Two of we a free like bird
So better they listen my word ♪
♪ When I say
Hold up your lighter and come ♪
♪ Flame inna de air, fire fi bun ♪
♪ Holla from the top of a mountain
And cry ♪
♪ Tell 'em say my love will never die ♪
♪ Where do we go? ♪
♪ A long and winding road ♪
♪ The louder they roar ♪
♪ The harder that they fall ♪
♪ Better we fall ♪
♪ Our time is borrowed ♪
♪ Live like it's our last day ♪
♪ There is no tomorrow ♪
♪ We'll be reborn ♪
♪ In a beautiful morning ♪
♪ Blowing like tumbleweed ♪
♪ Night come like thief ♪
♪ Till rooster crow ♪
♪ I know, I know we'll... ♪
♪ Hold up your lighter and come ♪
♪ Flame inna de air, fire fi bun ♪
♪ Holla from the top of a mountain
And cry ♪
♪ Tell 'em
Say my love will never die ♪
♪ Where do we go? ♪
♪ A long and winding road ♪
♪ The louder they roar ♪
♪ The harder that they fall ♪
♪ Every day we go harder ♪
♪ For the night, we live faster ♪
♪ When the rain come down harder ♪
♪ Light a flame, we go faster ♪
♪ For the pain will try test we ♪
♪ No Wahala can best we ♪
♪ Better know we don't lazy ♪
♪ Better know we go crazy ♪
♪ Every day we go harder ♪
♪ For the night, we live faster ♪
♪ When the rain come down harder ♪
♪ Light a flame, we go faster ♪
♪ For the pain will try test we ♪
♪ No Wahala can best we ♪
♪ Better know we don't lazy ♪
♪ Better know we go crazy ♪
♪ Every day we go hard ♪
♪ For the night, we live fast ♪
♪ When the rain come down hard ♪
♪ Light a flame, we go fast ♪
♪ Go bring dem, come we go ♪
♪ Go louder, silence no ♪
♪ Come fire, water go ♪
♪ Sing higher, cry no mo' ♪
♪ Nobody came for we
We tired, oh ♪
♪ Fire the flame they see
We stronger, oh ♪
♪ Every day we go harder ♪
♪ For the night, we live faster ♪
♪ When the rain come down harder ♪
♪ Light a flame, we go faster ♪
♪ For the pain will try test we ♪
♪ No Wahala can best we ♪
♪ Better know we don't lazy ♪
♪ Better know we go crazy ♪
♪ Every day we go harder ♪
♪ For the night, we live faster ♪
♪ When the rain come down harder ♪
♪ Light a flame, we go faster ♪
♪ For the pain will try test we ♪
♪ No Wahala can best we ♪
♪ Better know we don't lazy ♪
♪ Better know we go crazy ♪
♪ For the pain will try test we ♪
♪ No Wahala can best we ♪
♪ Better know we don't lazy ♪
♪ Better know we go crazy ♪
♪ And upon my return ♪
♪ You'll see a changed soul ♪
♪ The road was far too long ♪
♪ They'll run from me ♪
♪ As they ran from you ♪
♪ The fear in me ♪
♪ Is in a distant view ♪
♪ And there ain't no turning around ♪
♪ Here I go, no mercy for the sinner ♪
♪ Don't you ever turn around ♪
♪ Here I go ♪
♪ It hurts within the winter ♪
♪ Never, ever make a sound ♪
♪ Don't you ever ♪
♪ Never, ever ♪
♪ Make a sound ♪
♪ And upon my return ♪
♪ You'll see a changed soul ♪
♪ The road was far too long ♪
♪ They'll run from me ♪
♪ As they ran from you ♪
♪ The fear in me ♪
♪ Is in a distant view ♪
♪ And there ain't no turning around ♪
♪ No, there ain't... ♪
不在桌旁，儿子。
来吧。
嗯嗯。
恩典第一。
你比较清楚。
父亲，我们聚集在这里，以您的名义分享这种食物。
主啊，祝福这些食物进入我们的身体。
主啊，祝福我们的心和我们所做的一切，使我们可以奉你的名而行......
这个时候会是谁呢？
我不知道。
不。
♪ 三三十年 ♪
♪ 我试过了 ♪
♪ 忘记 ♪
♪ 我哭过的所有眼泪 ♪
放过我的家人吧。
西奥多。
没关系。
♪ 那个很久以前就认识我的人…… ♪
把他们排除在外。
你的争吵与我有关。
我们出去走走走走
并处理我们的业务。
- 请。
- 不。
不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不。
拜托，我求求你了。
不！
不！ 不！ 不！ 不！
不！ 不！ 不！
不！ 不！ 请！
不！
不！ 不，不，不，不，不！ 不！
埃斯帕萨神父？
我是来告白的……
和集合。
你知道我的硬币迟到会发生什么。
一个人有什么能力在他的手上画一只蝎子？
打扰一下？
一条蛇，
我明白那个。
伊甸园、圣经等等。
但是蝎子？
嗯，这让我很困惑。
你是谁？
只是一个男人。
在这里杀蝎子。
耶稣科尔特斯。
那是，呃，不同的时代。
不管你我之间发生了什么，一定是很久很久以前的事了。
不。
请。
一世...
对不起。
结束了吗？
这是一个通缉犯。
交出他的尸体，你会为你的教会得到 5,000 美元。
你为什么不自己收留他？
我值十。
♪ 阿瓦隆该死 ♪
♪ 去异国他乡 ♪
♪ 我把我的剑放在沙子里 ♪
♪ 我和男人和解了 ♪
♪ 他们举行了一场激烈的盛宴 ♪
♪ 我的眼睛所能看到的 ♪
♪ 我在寻找金色的羊毛 ♪
♪ 总有一天你会平静 ♪
♪ 所以不要诱惑我的手 ♪
♪ 我只是个男人 ♪
♪ 一个致命的场景，一个风化的人 ♪
♪ 男人必须在士兵躺下的地方哭泣 ♪
♪ 在受威胁的土地上 我的枪响了 ♪
♪ 我可以让枪声响起 ♪
♪ 我让所有的枪都爆炸了 ♪
♪ 用开关点十七它会改变你 ♪
♪ 妈妈总是说你是天使 ♪
♪ 爸爸得到了鬼魂 但他从未穿过这些门 ♪
♪ 他有鬼 但他从未穿过那些墙 ♪
♪ 教堂里的彩色玻璃窗我希望你能防污 ♪
♪ 因为当潮汐改变时，我试图玷污你 ♪
♪ 谋划报复 也挖你的坟墓 ♪
♪ 你想刻什么 你的墓碑也会说些什么 ♪
♪ 十字架在天使的头上 ♪
♪ 父亲的罪孽使门阶变暗 我变成了你 ♪
♪ 忠诚到最后 ♪
♪ 带有你名字的子弹把公鸡拉回来，瞄准，射击，砰 ♪
♪ 脆弱的生活 反映我们留下的过去 ♪
♪ 为了新事物 ♪
♪ 破碎的微笑，打开窗户 到我们试图隐藏的伤口 ♪
♪ 刻在阴暗的房间 ♪
♪ 飞翔的鸟 ♪
是的！
♪ 我回来时 ♪
♪ 看到一个改变的灵魂 ♪
♪ 那条路很远 ♪
♪ 而且太长了 ♪
♪ 他们会逃离我 ♪
♪ 当他们逃离你时 ♪
♪ 我内心的恐惧 ♪
♪ 在遥远的…… ♪
♪ 查看 ♪
这是Nat Love Gang！
别开枪了！ 别开枪了！
是一个人！ 我们把他钉住了！
等他的头露出来，然后吹掉那个混蛋。
要有耐心。
我听说耐心是一种美德。
但我一直迫不及待地想看看这混蛋是不是真的。
- 吉姆·贝克沃斯。
- 格莱姆兄弟。
这是带有“S”的格莱姆斯，你这个自负的狗屎。
我记得有一段时间你们所有的头巾都是深红色的。
被称为深红兜帽帮。
他们混蛋现在是粉红色的。
你知道，妈妈常说，“吉姆真是个好孩子。” 你知道我说了什么吗？
“妈妈，他妈的吉姆！看看他对我他妈的眼睛做了什么！”
- 我很甜。
- 你不甜。
- 你不是。
- 婊子，我很甜。
- 你知道吗？
我宁愿死也不愿听这个混蛋继续说话。
哇。
非常感谢，混蛋。
这他妈是什么鬼
当我的屁股被击中时玩速成游戏？
嘿嘿嘿。 你拿到了你的幸运币，不是吗？
长大了，吉姆。 这是真正的大人狗屎。 我们可以死。
但我们不会死。
因为我很容易被责备。 承认吧。
你知道，你可能会，但我听说有一个快速抽奖
比你更闪电，以切诺基比尔的名义。
“切诺基比尔。”
你道听途说。
你不说。
所以我说他妈的切诺基比尔。
你知道，与其抱怨，不如为我的表现鼓掌。
唯一应该从你的黑屁股嘴里说出来的话......
- “黑屁股嘴唇”？  -...应该...
- ...gracias.
- 那很顺利。
- 我知道。
- 黑色的嘴唇是美丽的嘴唇。
- 你会停止接触吗，黑人？
- 该死的。
你刚刚杀了我的兄弟。
你的同父异母兄弟，冷静点。 看起来你的日子有点糟糕。
当你发现你搞砸了谁的钱时，比你们这些狗娘养的要好。
更正。  你干了谁。
你们都抢银行。 我们抢劫你们。
从这里到非洲的黑人不会知道我们的存在。
你以为我说的是银行？
♪ 我不知道 ♪
♪ 他们去哪里-哦-哦-哦-哦 ♪
♪ 人类的孩子在哪里？  ♪
♪ 我们不知道的问题 ♪
♪ 不知道 ♪
♪ 我们什么时候才能再见到他们？  ♪
♪ 我们不知道的问题 ♪
♪ 不知道 ♪
♪ 献给王后和国王 闪亮的事物 ♪
♪ 他们给了我们灵魂 ♪
♪ 但他们很快就明白 自由胜过黄金 ♪
♪ 哦，旧日时光 ♪
♪ 旧日时光 ♪
♪ 这些都是不为人知的故事 ♪
晚上，绅士。 请检查您的武器并享受庆祝活动。
这是驿马车玛丽的地方，是不是不允许持枪？
'Cept for Mary's，自然。
自然。
自然而然地，她把一只像你这样的新面孔放在了这里来照顾它。
哦，我得看很多东西，爱先生。
人们看到我，并不会因为他们看到的东西而感到害怕。 看？
我们熟悉吗？
不，但你在这些地方很有名。
人们说你曾经用一颗子弹杀死了三个人。
现在，我还没有遇到一个能做到这一点的人。 打扰一下。
晚上，先生们。 请检查您的武器并享受您的夜晚。
我会尽快检查我的右臂，男孩。
然后您可以前往 Jourdon Anderson's。
你可以拿着武器在那边喝酒。
我们在这里喝酒，你这个小屁孩。
嘿！
无论如何，有些人倾向于有一种感觉。
把他们带到布朗医生那里。
把他们的枪带到警长那里。
当他们离开城镇时，他们可以把它们拿回来。
他们叫你什么？
他们叫我库菲。
这就是我在这里的原因！
不要伤害任何人！
- ♪ 一个！  ♪
- ♪ 得到那匹马和他的马车 ♪
- ♪ 两个！  ♪
- ♪ 抓住那个男人和他的步枪 ♪
- ♪ 三！  ♪
- ♪ 得到那个牧师和他的圣经 ♪
- ♪ 四！  ♪
- ♪ 为那些抵达时死去的人 ♪
- ♪ 五！  ♪
- ♪ 祈祷者看见天堂 ♪
- ♪ 六！  ♪
- ♪ 那些看不见魔鬼的人 ♪
- ♪ 七！  ♪
- ♪ 分离但平等 ♪
- ♪ 八！  ♪
- ♪ 说他们奴役我的人民 ♪
- ♪ 九！  ♪
- ♪ 所以打破他们的锁链和镣铐 ♪
♪ 十个！  ♪
再来。
- ♪ 一个！  ♪
- ♪ 得到那匹马和它的马车 ♪
- ♪ 两个！  ♪
- ♪ 抓住那个男人和他的步枪 ♪
- ♪ 三！  ♪
- ♪ 得到那个牧师和他的圣经 ♪
- ♪ 四！  ♪
- ♪ 为那些抵达时死去的人 ♪
- ♪ 五！  ♪
- ♪ 祈祷者看见天堂 ♪
- ♪ 六！  ♪
- ♪ 那些看不见魔鬼的人 ♪
- ♪ 七！  ♪
- ♪ 分离但平等 ♪
- ♪ 八！  ♪
- ♪ 说他们奴役我的人民 ♪
- ♪ 九！  ♪
- ♪ 所以打破他们的锁链和镣铐 ♪
♪ 十个！  ♪
没有了。
你还不跟我说话？
出去。
什么？
我说离开。
那这个吻是为了什么？
提醒你它是什么。
那是提醒你它是什么。
打扰一下。
袖口，把这个人收拾干净。
- 哦，是的，女士。
- 谢谢。
二楼。 左边第三个房间。
玛丽。
我唯一需要听到的就是“再见，玛丽”。
你永远不会再听到我说的一件事。
直到下一次你听到有人告诉你某个让你肮脏的人的下落。
他们一个都没有离开。
所以你找到蝎子了吗？
玛丽，现在这个世界上唯一对我有意义的东西
是你。
那纳特爱帮呢？
自从你离开后就不是什么帮派了。
只有我，吉姆，比尔。
下次他们来的时候，我会整理一下。
嗯。
你知道，我几乎可以相信这一点。
几乎，因为你没有得到最后一个，是吗？
你可以说出他的名字，玛丽。
鲁弗斯·巴克呢？
鲁弗斯在尤马度过了他的余生。
对于他这样的人来说，这比死还要糟糕。
只要那个人吸一口气，你的灵魂就会像以前一样被诅咒和狂野。
唔。
我做了东西，
我建造了东西，我不会因为你决定回来而冒险。
- “Trottin'”？
- 是的。
- 好吧，好吧。  - 嗯嗯。
我想我来错沙龙了
因为我没有和我自以为认识的玛丽·菲尔兹说话。
- 是的。 事情变了。
- 我看到。
嗯嗯。
因为玛丽...
那个玛丽...
...不要回避什么。
Apache 叫你什么？
狼娘？
不，这是皮克特过去常说的胡说八道。
这是皮克特过去常说的胡说八道。
- 阿帕奇叫我土狼女人。
- 唔。
是的，狼娘更喜欢。
我的帽子。
那里。
我进来了。
现在，狼夫人，不要把我的头从我脖子上吹下来。
- 纳特。
- 皮克特。
你得到了计时史上最糟糕的计时。
哦，你们都在做爱？
我道歉。
但我要向你展示的东西等不及了。
好吧，好吧，好吧。
如果这不是温文尔雅的蠢货自己。
哇，轻松，纳特。 先听听男人怎么说。
所以他可以告诉我他告诉你的同样的故事吗？
我他妈的为什么要撒谎？
鲁弗斯·巴克在他的余生中都被关在监狱里。
- 他要出去了。
- 如何？
如果我知道就该死。
我只知道是这样。
所有的帮派都准备再次为他骑行。
一半是他的。
而你们这些傻瓜拿了他的钱。
你认为鲁弗斯·巴克会让你保留那一半的钱，
你说我是个傻瓜？
我想我是。
在你的脚上。
呼气。
现在离开这里。
离开。
你在做什么'？ 我们可以杀死最后一个深红头巾。
它被称为深红色兜帽帮。 你以为这是最后一个？
是的。
我敢打赌我的左六射手他会杀死那个男孩。
如果那个人说的是实话，纳特只会让他更糟。
♪ 哇，看到了！ 我来了！  ♪
♪ 我来了！  ♪
你到底在外面干什么？
那不是没有办法登上火车，你该死的笨蛋...
你知道，他可能会说 nincompoop。
我们不是傻瓜。
如果他们说的话甚至以“N”开头，
他们会遇到同样的命运。
让他们看看你的脸。
好吧，大家保持冷静。 不要......嘿，不要碰任何东西。
我叫切诺基比尔。
现在让大家知道，我并不特别喜欢暴力。
话虽如此，您目前与极端暴力的人在一起。
尝试一些。
啊。 拉屎。
所以，不要做蠢事。 好的？
快下车吧，你这个没有妈妈的人渣。
你一定是英雄。
大神，为什么总有一个？
你粗鲁。
我可能真的很喜欢对你施加暴力。
但谁知道呢？
也许你会赢。
让我们来看看。
明白我的意思了吗？
现在，让开，这样我们就可以毫不费力地在这里结束我们的工作。
好吧，大家...
停在那儿。
不。
我说停。
放下武器，男孩。
或者我们杀死这列火车上的每个人。
我说把枪放下。
没关系。
那辆车上还有士兵吗？
有。
究竟是多少？
三十。
十！
看，这就是你要说的。
打开门。
我说打开该死的门。
我们到了。
我亲爱的营。
我想你把所有的大炮都对准了门。
我想告诉你，在那扇门前，有一个你自己的部队。
任何穿过那扇门的子弹都会先击中他，好吗？
说出你的名字，罪犯。
哦，我不是罪犯，先生，嗯，但我的名字是切诺基比尔。
你叫什么名字？
我的名字是该死的法律的执行官。
你让那个士兵立即离开。
现在离开这列火车，没有人会受伤。
哦，这听起来像是在谈论恐惧，该死的法律主持先生。
我们已经伤害了几个人。
你只是想让我们逍遥法外吗？
说出你的目的，混蛋。
还有，我不是混蛋。
但是你已经得到了我们想要的东西。 我们有你想要的士兵。
现在，我建议我们进行和平交易，每个人都可以活着看到新的一天。
- 听起来很花哨？
- 让男孩走吧。
杰克！
我没事，爸爸！
那只是皮肉伤，先生。
你有十秒钟的时间放下你的枪，打开这扇该死的门，否则你这里的小亲戚就会灭亡。
进一步伤害他，我会杀死你们最后一个不敬虔的狗娘养的。
该死的，特鲁迪。 你知道我喜欢我的倒计时。
我很抱歉，先生。 我这里的朋友不喜欢算术。
不管怎样，七秒。
六。
- 放下你的步枪。
- 五。
我说把它们放下。
四。
三。
好吧，好吧。 非常感谢你。 走吧，男孩。
继续走。 继续前进。 没有人做任何愚蠢的事情。
就像你被教导的那样走路。
左，右，左。 左，右，左。
左，右，左。
♪ 跳到 Lou，亲爱的 ♪
- 打开它。
- 我不能。
钥匙回到尤马。 而接下来...
再一次。
你会因此被追到天涯海角。
我不喜欢长途跋涉，艾伯特中将。
有没有想过为什么你被赋予将一个孤独的歹徒从一个监狱运送到另一个监狱的任务？
完全赦免巴克先生和他的所有同伙犯下的所有罪行。
署名乔治·普赖斯将军。
这是关于什么的？
好吧，他带着一个提议来找我们。
杀死该死的法律的特定官员。
一个如此狡猾的人，连政府都为他的罪行感到尴尬。
显然，你和你的男人消灭了整个城镇，包括妇女和儿童，
偷银子。
- 现在，这是一些不道德的狗屎。
- 不道德的狗屎。
请。 我会分...
嘘。
不！
啪！ 不，不，不，不，不。
帕。
不。
这里谁能开火车？
我说...
除了他之外的所有人。
♪ 哇，看到了！ 我来了！  ♪
♪ 我很宽阔 ♪
♪ 我比百老汇宽 ♪
晚上，先生。 和我一起检查你的武器，享受夜晚剩下的一切。
哦，没必要给我看那颗星。 我知道你是谁。
不过，在这里，我是警长，这让玛丽女士成为元帅。
元帅说：“不要让任何人进来这里被枪杀，否则他们可能会被枪杀。”
我的徽章不同意。
检查你的枪带。
打扰一下。
那么你打算如何收留我，元帅？
死盯着我看？
只是死亡又如何？
只是一根管子。
你介意？
从来不知道你去碰它。
只有在我杀了一个人之后。
或者之前。
由于堪萨斯城的一起银行抢劫案，我正在追查
Crimson Hood Gang。
原来有人在我之前得到了他们。
你知道我不抢劫银行，元帅。
但是你抢劫他们这样做，这对我来说都是一样的。
- 德克萨斯州。
- 什么？
抢劫发生时我在德克萨斯州。
你怎么知道什么时候发生的？
每当发生银行抢劫案时，我都在德克萨斯州。
当然，除非抢劫发生在德克萨斯州。
我听到的方式，其中一些是带着深红色兜帽的男孩
是新的 Rufus Buck 帮的一部分，Nat。
尤马的鲁弗斯。
他出来。 但你已经知道了，不是吗？
当你应该出去围捕你的小副手时，你为什么坐在这里独白，喝我的威士忌？
因为他被赦免了，纳特。
鲁弗斯·巴克被赦免了他无数的掠夺行为。
看到我一直在寻找银行劫匪之类的地形，
那条特别的消息没能传到我这里。
他们在说什么？
关于枪的东西，杀人。
你为什么让那个孩子拿走我的枪？ 这是什么愚蠢的规则？
- 应该是四支枪指向...
- 闭嘴，皮克特。
你开枪，他死了。
你想念，
你们都死了。
你过来。
拿着这些袖口。 铐住这个人。
或者我现在把三个放在他的胸口，减少麻烦。
继续。
告诉这个年轻的雄鹿备份。
容易，吉姆。
这里的每个人都知道我是谁。
我要带 Nat Love 去 Fort Smith 接受审判。
任何人都试图跟随我，
你们都知道我在做什么。
来吧。
你们都享受晚上剩下的时间。
♪ 好吧，现在 ♪
♪ 哇哦，好吧 ♪
♪ 应许之地 ♪
♪ 前往应许之地 ♪
♪ 是的，应许之地 ♪
♪ 哦，天哪 ♪
♪ 前往应许之地 ♪
♪ 下到瓦斯马拉 ♪
♪ 然后我们在亚的斯亚贝巴停留 ♪
♪ 前往沙沙曼大陆 ♪
♪ 在国王大道上骑行 ♪
♪ 前往应许之地 ♪
♪ 天哪 ♪
♪ 是的，应许之地 ♪
鲁弗斯。
切诺基比尔，史密斯女士，早上好。
巴克先生，很高兴您回到雷德伍德，先生。
关于堪萨斯城银行的任何消息？
Crimson Hoods 以 25,000 美元的价格购买了它。
可他们还没来得及，就遭到了伏击。
每个人都知道从我们这里带走是自杀。
显然有人不同意。
他妈的。 那只是让我们回到了开始的地方。
我们应该如何在没有任何砖块的情况下建造麦加？
我们得把它从我们自己的银行里拿出来。
我们没有那种钱，特鲁迪。
我们只拿到了超过 2,500 美元的几便士。
他说什么？
- 2,500...
- 我听到了。
- 威利。
- 是的。
当然很热，不是吗？
怎么了，小家伙？
- 你想看什么吗？
- 是的。
现在看这个。 不要把你的眼睛从它身上移开。
哦，它还在！
鲁弗斯·巴克。
看着你。
昔日的遗物，什么也没有。
你以为你可以滚进我的城镇，拿走属于我的东西？
你他妈的以为我是谁，嗯？
是不是没有人害怕你，是不是没有人跑'。
我也是个阴险的混蛋。
我的手指轻轻一按，你就消失了。
所以我建议你离开...
在我吃完牛排之前。
如果你甚至考虑坚持......
进来吧。
怎么了，卡森？
警长，巴克先生想见你。
告诉那个人，我没有什么可对他说的。
这不是请求。
威利·埃斯科。
鲁弗斯。
当我在监狱里腐烂时，你想卖掉这个小镇吗？
你熟悉的世界已经消失。
有洪水来了。
你认为当它发生时你能抓住这个地方吗？
至少我知道的足够多，可以得到我的然后出去。
杀了我...
而你将一无所有。
你知道，像你这样的人会让我们都屈从到我们的日子结束
只要你能给自己买房子，徽章，
还有他们该死的金牙。
你想在这里做吗？
你去吧。 这就是你想要的，对吧？
这就是你来这里的目的？
我不会让你失望的。 来吧。
这就是你想要的。 想要更多？
你想要更多，对吧？ 你还要一些吗？
过来，混蛋。
干得好。
妈的。 我做了打金。
嗨男孩。 过来。 来，拿那个金子。 得到那块金子。
好的。 告诉你妈妈你现在很有钱！ 前进！
现在，我不会杀了你，威利。
你我曾经是朋友。
但知道这一点。
红木永远不会是你的，永远不会。
绝不。
事实上，这里不再欢迎你了。
现在...
我要你立即撤离，否则就死在你躺着的地方。
说什么？
没错。
♪ 回家见我的主 ♪
♪ 我要回家 ♪
♪ 我现在要回家见我的主 ♪
♪ 我要回家见我的主 ♪
你可以把这些取下来一段时间。
是的。
告诉我一件事。 你怎么知道Rufus会在Redwood？
他正在从他们的 Crimson Hoods 那里拿走这笔钱。
那就是他要去的地方。
现在你和一名元帅联手带他进来。
我不会带他进来。我要让他失望。
而且我们不合作，老头。
你的生命是可消耗的，元帅。 我的帮派不是。
妈的，既然我们在这里，我应该告诉你......
我是想杀了你...
当你和你的伙伴们带来鲁弗斯时。
很多男人都在修理，儿子。
他们似乎总是在完成工作之前就死了。
只是为了记录...
我一个人收留了鲁弗斯。
玛丽。
我想你现在已经到了史密斯堡的一半了。
你可以放下那把枪，元帅。 这不是伏击。
另一方面，您可能希望随身携带。
你认为我愚蠢到会爱上你们在我的沙龙里扯的那些废话吗？
我不想让你再混进去了。
那你应该告诉我的。
我必须承认自己有一些原始的感觉。
这不是没有路可以请朋友旅行。
现在你拿走我们从 Crimson Hoods
上取下的钱，然后买下你一直喋喋不休的牧场。 唔？
你真是太慷慨了，但这不是这个帮派的运作方式。
在通常的地方住宿，准备在我们回来时以三种方式分享。
这是不是没有回来。
现在离开这里。
你们所有人。 这不是你的战斗。
你亲自对付魔鬼，你需要的不仅仅是你和元帅。
我看到了魔鬼，而鲁弗斯·巴克不是他。
恶魔的白色。
你有想死的理由吗，吉姆？
除了你救我脱离这个？
此外，梦露说切诺基比尔和鲁弗斯一起跑。
每次我谈到我的速度时，一个混蛋都想把切诺基比尔拉出来。
我要一劳永逸地结束这场争论。
就像他们在克拉伦斯之书中所说的那样，“没有人能超越我。”
超速不是一个词，克拉伦斯也不是没有书。
我希望切诺基在你的屁股上放了一颗子弹只是为了让你闭嘴。
- 嘿。
- 你把这些留在了我的墙上，爱先生。
想到我们要追捕恶棍，你会需要他们。
有义务的。
还在等什么？
你认为命运正在向你走来？
嘻嘻！ 走！
是的。 我知道。
前进。
♪ 哇哈拉他们走了 哇哈拉他们来了 ♪
♪ 哇哈拉他们骑 哇哈拉他们跑 ♪
♪ 他们唱歌哇哈拉 ♪
♪ 哇哈拉他们走了 哇哈拉他们来了 ♪
♪ 哇哈拉他们骑 哇哈拉他们跑 ♪
♪ 哇哈拉 他们唱他们叫的哇哈拉 ♪
♪ 哇哈拉他们飞 哇哈拉他们跌倒 ♪
♪ 哇哈拉他们走了 哇哈拉他们来了 ♪
♪ 哇哈拉他们骑 哇哈拉他们跑 ♪
我看起来怎么样？
好的。
大家都在吗？
大概。
你怎么能做到？
把这一切都留给威利？
如果你在跑红木，
谁会继续进行手术？
还有谁会让所有的帮派保持一致？
听着，我知道威利有他的方法，但他曾经忠诚过。
忠诚是一种美德，鲁弗斯。
直到它不是。
你忠于我？
看到这里的这些人了吗？
他们要么看不到，要么不想看。
但我相信你在做什么。
这个地方可以成为我们的乐土。
只要是这样，我就不会不做任何事情来完成它。
你告诉他们。
红木市民。
新的一天即将来临。
到目前为止，您无疑已经了解到，该领土将正式开放供定居。
现在他们说我们拥有的一切都将成为我们自己的。
但你和我一样知道那值多少钱。
你看，你的土地、你的生意、你的房子都被承诺给出价最高的人
由你的前任警长威利·埃斯科 (Wiley Escoe) 提供。
现在，巴克先生可以防止这种情况发生。
但为了让我们做到这一点，我们有必要征税。
我们要付出什么代价？
- 50,000 美元。
- 哦。
你可以从这个镇上每一个活生生的灵魂身上榨取每一分钱，但它不会接近那个。
你让我们介于岩石和坚硬的地方之间。
你在这个国家生活了多久？
岩石和坚硬的地方就是我们所说的星期一。
我听说过鲁弗斯·巴克。
他是一个多么糟糕的人。
但他之前曾被关进监狱，
我想他很快就会回到那里。
他在的时候，也许我会回到这个小镇。
因为我不付钱。
你认为我为自己制作了红木？
什么目的？
红木不是藏身之处，因为我不藏。
这不是梦。
我不做梦。
你知道这是什么？
这是一个例子。
这是一个例子...
供其他人跟随。
和你...
你是进步的敌人。
请。 请。
- 我有一个家庭。
- 你叫什么名字？
詹姆士。
安息吧，詹姆斯。
现在，多少钱？
能集齐多少？
万。
也许是 15，如果每一分钱都可以挤出来的话。
嗯嗯。
在我们收集所有物品之前，不会有人离开城镇。
如果你不遵守，
你和你爱的一切都会燃烧。
我没有什么可抢劫的。
但我有人要开枪。
下台。
威利·埃斯科。
巴斯·里夫斯。
他妈的。
红木与枪手一起爬行。
Rufus 拿了 12 个，拿走了我的 6 个。
谁知道他现在得到了多少。
我不相信这个人说的话。
他是侦察员。
我说我们杀了他。
我们把剩下的牙齿拔掉。
你打过警长吗，男孩？
市长？
比射杀普通人难一点。
而我两者都是。
你们都活着，死了，因为鲁弗斯不喜欢散漫的结局。
除非你有内幕消息，否则法律不要找到像鲁弗斯巴克这样的人。
是不是，威利？
如果我按照我的方式，你就在鲁弗斯旁边的监狱下面。
但是您与自己达成了交易，结果反而佩戴了徽章。
你有你想要鲁弗斯离开的理由，我也有我的。
敌人的敌人不是朋友吗？
鲁弗斯试图拯救雷德伍德。 但为此，他需要钱。
这是他没有的一件事。
好吧，看这里。 你和魔鬼做了一笔交易。
现在他来收了。
你好好休息，
但在日出之前离开。
或者它会从坏到坏。 你听？
哦。
元帅。
元帅。 元帅。
所有这些诡计都会让你丧命，儿子。
听着，元帅。
我比任何武器都快。 你可以相信这一点。
我看到的更快。
好的。 在哪里？
镜子里。
黑人说：“在镜子里。”
我很……对不起。
我宁愿骑着黑马骑着一匹金色的种马参加枪战。
- 他妈的这是什么意思？
- 闪亮的狗屎被击中。
你要拍我？
你怎么看，律师？
我想你们都会死。
♪ 随风而去 ♪
♪ 她走了 ♪
♪ 随着她花园的成长 ♪
♪ 握紧那些花 ♪
♪ 随风而去 ♪
♪ 她走了 ♪
我会在 sunup 前回来提供信息。
信息从哪里来？
红木。
你知道我们不能相信威利的话。
在我们采取下一步行动之前，必须有人了解这片土地。
是的，玛丽，但有人不一定是你。
领土上的每个枪手都会在你下马的那一刻认出你。
比尔和贝克沃斯也是如此。
如果你忘记了，你的脸比我们所有人的脸加起来还要出名，驿马车玛丽。
从这里到德克萨斯州的那间轿车的广告中得到了它。
这就是为什么我可以骑车进城的原因。
大家都知道我在买轿车。
鲁弗斯需要钱。 我要在特鲁迪·史密斯的位置上向他提出要约...
玛丽，我性格中的什么让你认为我会允许？
我不是在征求你的同意。
好的。
那我……我想我只会向你要你的。
既然你永远不会让男人放弃你，
我只需要直接问你。
那是我父亲给我母亲的戒指。
我本来打算在道格拉斯还给你的。
但你没有。
我现在是。
我曾经讨厌对你感到无助。
那些日子现在已经过去了。
玛丽...
当尘埃落定，我们将分道扬镳，永远。
但直到尘埃落定。 我在这里直到那时。
日出见。
♪ 女人哭泣，赋予生命 ♪
♪ 玛丽妈妈和婴儿 她一直背负的重担 ♪
♪ 女人的哭声赋予我们生命 ♪
♪ 她恳求他原谅我们 一直以来的罪和罪人 ♪
哇。
女士，您是 Redwood 的居民吗？
你没有足够的自信去问我住在哪里。
好吧，这把枪说回答了该死的问题。
算了，这枪不说了。
驿马车玛丽。
可怕的格特鲁德史密斯。
我自己更喜欢奸诈的特鲁迪，但我会接受。
是什么让你来到我的小镇？
我听说鲁弗斯·巴克回来了。
新闻传播得很快。
我有一个他可能想听的提议。
好吧，你得到的任何报价，
你可以给我做。
我不做生意的帮助。
给我那个狗屎。
带路，奸诈的特鲁迪。
♪ 星期一的孩子一直在微笑 ♪
♪ 周二的孩子会在里面玩耍 ♪
♪ 星期三有枪 ♪
♪ 星期四的眼泪才刚刚开始 ♪
♪ 周五的船都在哭泣 ♪
♪ 周一似乎很遥远 ♪
♪ 星期二一点也不差 ♪
♪ 星期三带着火焰 ♪
♪ 星期四永远不一样 ♪
♪ 周五的船不会回来 ♪
♪ 星期一的孩子被撕裂了 ♪
♪ 星期二的孩子被锁链扔了 ♪
♪ 星期三的孩子曾经微笑 ♪
♪ 星期四的眼泪现在是尼罗河 ♪
♪ 星期五的孩子在燃烧 ♪
说你的作品。
我假设你知道我是谁。
我想你知道我曾经和谁一起跑步。
无论如何，那些日子对我来说已经过去了，
但我没有把耳朵贴在地上就不能成为驿马车玛丽·菲尔兹
我的耳朵告诉我，你刚刚失去了 25 岁。
我希望你的提议能对抗你的神经......
请允许我完成的纬度。
我在道格拉斯的沙龙正在蓬勃发展。
在 Elks 给我买了另一家，我也在
Cascade 开了一家餐馆。
总而言之，我可以把这个从你手中拿走。
一提到我的名字就能带来好生意
任何附属机构，而，
恕我直言，但鲁弗斯·巴克这个名字让人害怕。
我们知道你是谁。
你带着那个提议走进我的小镇是有风险的。
除非有更多的风险，否则像你这样的女人不会把自己绑在这种风险上。
看，我不相信巧合，
就像你会在 Crimson Hoods
被我的钱伏击后马上走进这里一样。
你在想什么？
哎呀。
你一定忘记了门上写的是谁的名字。
再来一轮。
我们有一个派对，你们。 来吧。
好的，玛丽。
好的。
所以你还说你对那笔钱一无所知，你一个人来了？
没错。
你一路骑到这里来杀了自己。
为了什么？
爱情？
爱是唯一值得为之而死的东西。
但你对此一无所知。
你懂，
我有一个姐姐叫玛丽。
她很漂亮，意志坚强，和你一样。
她在我 11 岁时死于小儿麻痹症。
总是很痛苦，但她从不让我看到她哭。
嗯。
我们住着一个叫霍普的女孩。
大胖子，总是挑小孩子。
显然是出于嫉妒。
但她从不跟我操。
她充满激情地憎恨玛丽，
总是取笑她有多瘦多虚弱。
后来有一天，
希望路过我们家，
一只手拿着苹果，另一只手拿着刀片。
她决定把苹果扔到街对面的玛丽，
它击中了我姐姐的头部，使她失去平衡。
她从台阶上摔下来。
弄断了她的脚踝。
而现在那...
那是我第一次也是唯一一次亲眼看到我姐姐哭泣。
霍普站在那里嘲笑她那该死的丑陋面孔。
我爸...
他回到家，
他脱下腰带，打我不保护我妹妹。
他鞭打我，直到我全身麻木。
然后
他去霍普家对她做同样的事情。
当他到达那里时，他看到她全家站在房子的一边，所有人都在尖叫和哭泣，
还有希望……
躺在血泊中的地板上。
有人割开了她的喉咙。
用自己的刀杀了她。
爸爸无语了。
他回家后没跟我说一句话。
第二天，
他让我和祖父母住在一起。
然后下次我见到我姐姐的时候，
她躺在棺材里。
疾病杀死了她。
我很抱歉你姐姐不得不受苦。
我钦佩她的勇敢。
但你从我这里得不到任何消息。
你懂，
我真的很佩服你的勇敢。
但恐怕结局还是结局。
希望
一定死。
但尚未。
把她留在街上，让每个人都能看到她。
没有人来收集她的“日出前，在她的头上放一颗子弹”。
是的女士。
看来不用等那么久了。
谁先死，对吧？
- 谁先死。  - 嗯嗯。
让她起来。
“谁先死”？
现在，这是什么蠢话？
你们两个想在这里被枪杀？
纳特爱。 多么可预测。
你预测我的朋友比尔·皮克特瞄准的是你的圆顶礼帽？
在你的孩子们瞄准目标之前你就已经死了。
然后你就死了。
但是你的老板不会看到这笔钱的一分钱。
我的老板？
他在哪里？
谁在哪里？
元帅。
我在说英语，是吗？
- 对我来说听起来像英语。  - 嗯嗯。
鲁弗斯·巴克在哪里？
哦。
呵呵。
低音。
特鲁迪。
如果我知道你在改变立场，我会邀请你来加入我们的。
你是来救你遇险的姑娘的吗？
你看起来不难听。
所以我再问你一次。
鲁弗斯·巴克在哪里？
嗯，很明显，你不认识我。
告诉你的人去，
但你留下，
也许你的少女会活得久一点。
元帅。
哦。
虽然你很漂亮。
- 啊，把她的屁股放回去。
- 是的女士。
来给我喝
嘿。
我听到的快速抽奖是什么，切诺基比尔？
我听到你说得太快以至于你的对手没有时间画画
在你把两个放进去之前。
不，那不是我。
我是切诺基比尔，它会向说话太多的人开枪。
那我就让你轻松点。
你先画。
你以为这是什么？  “谁在西部抽签最快？”
一切都归结为谁禁食谁不禁食，对吧？
不，这一切都归结为谁活着谁死了。
特鲁迪，我要给我弄点喝的。
晚安。
嘿，嘿，喝，我的屁股，伙计。
- 我整晚都在练习这种对峙。
- 吉姆。
- 你不会走开。
- 离开这里。
- 不，没人...
- 离开这里，吉姆。
- 那只鸡...
- 现在不是时候
好的。 好的。
三月，男孩。
- 我说行军！
- 行进。
呼，二，三，四。
足够了。
他们打你不好？
我要把他们都杀了。
你熟悉拿破仑吗？
他说：“我被驱赶到一个我不知道的终点。”
“当我到达时，
因为我将变得不必要，
一个原子就足以粉碎我。”
“在此之前，人类的所有势力都无法阻止我。”
那是一个完全知道自己是谁的人。
最重要的是，
他知道他的时代即将结束。
砍倒他。
你知道为什么...
我给了你那个伤疤？
所以我会记得你。
不。
不，我给了你那道伤疤，所以当你回到我身边时我能认出你的脸。
纳特爱，
抢劫不法之徒的不法之徒，
不留情面地追捕侵犯他的人的死亡天使。
我知道你是谁。
我看到了你不会越过的界限。
看，我知道另一边是什么。
为殴打道歉。
这更多地表明，如果我们无法达成协议，菲尔兹女士可能会看到什么。
什么条款？
你会在周五中午之前归还你从我这里偷的钱。
不一会儿。
并且您将在此基础上增加 10,000 美元。 我们称之为兴趣。
有什么好笑的？
哦，该死，你怎么……你怎么认为我会明白的？
你要抢银行。
Nat Love 要去抢银行。
在此期间，我提前表示感谢。
来吧，打开它。
我希望周五能拿到钱。
所有的。
你知道我不能让你那样做。
如果三天后这笔钱不在鲁弗斯手里，玛丽就会死。
无论如何，我们谈论的是哪家银行？
梅斯维尔。
梅斯维尔？
那是一个白色的小镇。
是的，这就是为什么他们的银行里会有 10,000 美元。
这太疯狂了。
我的情绪很混乱。
我的意思是，皮克特，我同意。 这很疯狂。
但是，纳特，我也同意你告诉元帅我们无论如何都会做那件事。
那是一些真正的非法狗屎。
- 我们取缔，不是吗？
- 不是“我们”，吉姆。
在你在镇上拉的那件事之后，我们几乎都被杀了。
我有那个。
取回你从深红头巾那里拿走的钱。
皮克特，孩子，你跟我来。
如果鲁弗斯·巴克想把那家银行拿走，他为什么不派自己的手下呢？
这样他就干净了，明白吗？
我得像白天一样光着身子进去，
一个刚出道的银行劫匪，在全国各地张贴通缉海报。
在你开门之前，他们会像苍蝇一样在你身上。
是的。
我说我必须被认可。
前进。
一定不行。
对于玛丽。
哇！ 呼！
死里逃生。
关闭他妈的剃须！
我以为我爱上了一个小伙子。
这就是为什么我什么也没说。
好吧，我不是唯一的。 我不能...
我不能......不仅仅是我。 不仅仅是我。
只是你，吉姆。
♪ 跟随，跟随 他们跟随的人 ♪
♪ 他们认识的人都在抄袭 去我的石窟 ♪
♪ 他们把我看成精灵 试着把我关在瓶子里 ♪
♪ 小气，小人 把他们隔离起来 ♪
♪ 他们用绳子把你绑起来 他们像拨奏一样演奏黑鬼 ♪
现在吉杜普。
允许我。
你的真实姓名是什么？
Cuffee我的真名。
我出生时的名字？
国泰威廉姆斯。
国泰，你走路不如骑。
洛夫先生，我妈妈总是告诉我要尊重我的长辈，所以我不会说出我的想法。
没关系。 我能读懂你的心。
那么我很抱歉你不得不听到这个。
前进。
加油，亲爱的。
是的？
我想提款。
哦。
什么...
女士，您必须有一个帐户。
而且，好吧，我会为此推荐杰里科的一家银行或者红木银行。
哦。
我不是在谈论那种退缩。
我说话...
我在说...
谈论那种。
嘿，蓝眼睛。
你害怕。
你的手在颤抖。 你会想念的。
我不会。
呼气。
阿塔博伊。
我不喜欢我的搭档。
他不想向任何人开枪，但突然间，我有心了。
现在打开他妈的门。
觉得我现在很有趣吗？
你在看什么？
把所有的顾客都弄过来。
- 让他们过去！
- 好吧好吧。
- 请大家快点这边。
- 你也是。 移动！
时代变了，不是吗？
他们说抢劫银行是一项艰苦的工作。
那是谎言。 抢银行很容易。
困难的部分是在不杀戮的情况下做到这一点。
那么，会是什么...
经理先生？
好人。
来吧。 我们走吧。
来吧。 吉迪亚普。 走。
好啦好啦。
- 快乐银行与您。
- 好的，先生。
纳特爱。
甚至看起来不像很多。
不是它的样子。 这是它可以给你买的东西。
Rufus 拿到那笔钱后不会让 Mary 走的。
是的，我知道。
他会杀了她，让我走，所以我会随身携带伤害。
那又怎样，我们只是白白经历了那么多麻烦？
现在我们得到了他想要的东西。
就是这样？
必须是。
如果你愿意，你可以草率地射我，或者你可以等着看我先带什么。
哦。
鲁弗斯在这些山丘上都有这样的藏匿处。
一个小军队就够了。
不要没有人接受我来找我的东西。
甚至恶魔本人也不行。
鲁弗斯·巴克是个男人。
你们最好接受这个事实。
人或鬼，
这将是巴克在生者中的最后一天。
♪ 我回来时 ♪
♪ 看到一个改变的灵魂 ♪
- ♪ 那条路很远 ♪
- ♪ 太长了 ♪
- ♪ 他们会逃离我 ♪
- ♪ 当他们逃离你时 ♪
- ♪ 我内心的恐惧 ♪
♪ 在远处 ♪
♪ 是 ♪
♪ 在遥远的 ♪
♪ 查看 ♪
哇在那里，哇在那里。 哇。
下午。
我会叫你跑去找你的上司，但这就像要求你跑去找你爸爸一样。
可能是任何人，对吧？
唔。
你懂，
我愿意赌我的右臂
我的尸体数量比你多。
儿子，那是个糟糕的赌注。
我喜欢那首歌或你在那里吹口哨的任何东西。
走吧，杰瑞。 走。
那是我们的钱？
呃...
与我同行。
嘿，就……跟我走吧。
- 留意这个，天使。  - 嗯嗯。
你知道他们称你的老板为魔鬼吗？
连魔鬼也需要钱，对吧？
所以就像我们如何拥有那笔钱一样......
让我来规定参与条款。
那是什么鬼？ 那是什么鬼东西，老铁？
这是右臂还是左臂？
天啊。
嗯，现在我们...
有你们。
哇。
哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇哇
你可以在这里抓住你的好朋友。
你有一个吵闹的小流氓。
- 玛丽。
- 是的，我们会做到这一点。
- 我们要先数这个。
- 现在，切诺基。
或者你的老板会很快抽到 35,000 美元。
好的。
解开这匹马，让玛丽可以骑出去。
- 你总是动作这么慢？
- 你总是说这么多？
真的吗？
在后面？
你怎么看，贝克沃斯？
不，他不会那样做
因为那样我就得往他的颅骨里放一颗子弹。
我们永远不会知道现在谁是最快的，对吗？
我得把它交给你，男孩。
你知道如何做一个盛大的入口。
该死，我什至没有排练那个。
你知道，快速绘制，
Nat Love 是一个行走的死人。
但你不必如此。
你为什么不骑上你的马，拉屎，然后回到你称之为家的地方？
你知道那是不可能的。
从五开始倒数？
五...
四...
三...
为什么他们总是要数得这么慢？
吉姆！
吹那个婊子，比尔！
♪ 对他人做 ♪
♪ 你会让他们做的 ♪
杀了她。
♪ 哦，那个死神，他会赢的 ♪
♪ 所有活在罪中的人 ♪
♪ 给那位女士一个火环 ♪
♪ 你已死在血液中 ♪
♪ 那是你的女人 不是更好的爱 ♪
♪ 所有活在罪中的人 ♪
玛丽！
推！
♪ 你要躺着棺材，所以 ♪
特鲁迪是我的。
♪ 死在你的血液里 ♪
♪ 那是你的女人 不是更好的爱 ♪
今晚我们将为您演奏第一首曲子。
而第一首曲子叫做……
O l'oun t'awa se n'yara。 杰卡贝雷
意思是，
“让我们开始我们进入房间要做的事情。”
我们走吧。
♪ 一、二、三！  ♪
王八蛋！
呼气，混蛋。
来吧。
- 他们从哪里弄到你的？
- 肩膀。 下来！
火柴。
你现在想抽烟吗？
比赛，巴斯。
好的。
跳吧，混蛋。
他妈的。
我一直知道是你
谁放弃了我。
上帝知道我的心。
再见，老朋友。
鲁弗斯，我别无选择……
我告诉了那个孩子。
他们该死的把戏...
对不起，女士们。
- 你没事吧，库菲？
- 只需要重新加载。
你看起来很受伤，皮克特先生。
只是皮肉伤口而已。 玛姬今天还没准备好迎接我。
嗯？
什么鬼？
我会被诅咒的。
皮克特！
现在，为什么你的脸上有那种表情？
不，不，不，不，兄弟，不，不，不。
停下。 不要那样做。
你有一个选择。
你总是有选择的。
害怕只会在来世给你带来恶业。
他连机会都没有，你个王八蛋！
你也要朝我背后开枪？ 还是欺骗计数？
♪ 我在猛烈的罪恶中失去了影子 ♪
♪ 从来不知道搜索会在 ♪
贝克沃斯的速度更快。
♪ 画了一张我唯一的愿望 ♪
♪ 带我回到 Blackskin Mile ♪
♪ 我以为我的业力就是我的命运 ♪
♪ 从未见过太阳 直到为时已晚 ♪
♪ 还有哦 ♪
♪ 描绘我的孤独 追逐每一个高潮 ♪
♪ 带我回到 Blackskin Mile ♪
♪ 我从未见过疯子的灵魂 ♪
♪ 我没有看到我所拥有的东西的倒影 ♪
♪ 但我知道外面有更好的东西 ♪
♪ 所以你不把我带回黑皮一英里吗？  ♪
照顾我的朋友。
纳特。
千万不要错过。
拿起你的枪。
我知道现在是什么。
是眼睛。
把它们捡起来，我说。
你的父亲，
他是个好人吗？
他是。
在你砍掉他们之前，我妈妈是个好女人。
看来我们的成长经历不同。
我不在乎你是如何长大的。
现在拿起你的枪转身。
我过去常常看着我父亲把他的食物煮过头，把我妈妈打得一塌糊涂。
如果她也没有煮熟，他就把她切得很好。
有一天，我决定介入，
他向我发怒。
我父亲不是一个好人。
不是一个好人。 他是个不法分子。
罗宾银行...
他喜欢喝酒。
我妈妈拿了一个瓶子，切了他来保护我。
他回击她，就这样，她走了。
然后，就像他是个胆小鬼一样，
他带走了我们所有的东西然后离开了
离开我和我的...
我的母亲。
我才十岁，你知道...
和你差不多年纪...
当我给你那个伤疤的时候。
我不得不照顾自己，但我变成了现在的我，
就像你一样。
就像我所做的那样，我所能想到的就是希望我父亲为他所做的事情付出代价。
我找了他很多年，一直找不到。
就好像他从地球上消失了一样。
我并没有停下来。 我一直在找...
直到我找到了他。
一天...
瞧，
他在那里，
我的父亲，
一个新人。
他现在很干净。
清醒。
神之人。
有一个教堂。
他有一个漂亮的小妻子。
他还有一个儿子，
十岁左右，
他的眼睛像我一样闪耀。
你在说谎。
你在说谎！
杀了我们的父亲是报应，但是……
我的父亲！
我的妈妈！
但这还不够。
让你活着，
这才是真正的报复。
你犯下的每一个罪，你抢劫的每一家银行，你杀死的每一个人。
我的意思是，看着你。
你他试图逃避的一切。
巴克。
把他的名字改成了“爱”。
你一个巴克。
你在说谎。
就像我。
就像他一样。
但你更好。 你甚至会超过我，因为...
我不能杀死我的兄弟。
然而在这里你要杀死你的人。
是时候报仇了，纳撒尼尔·巴克。
继续。
- 纳撒尼尔巴克。
- 不。
报仇雪恨。
纳撒尼尔·巴克。
报仇雪恨吧！
你一个巴克。
纳撒尼尔·巴克。
纳撒尼尔...
♪ 我回来时 ♪
♪ 你会看到一个改变的灵魂 ♪
♪ 道路 ♪
♪ 太长了 ♪
恶魔死了吗？
我不知道。
♪ 他们会逃离我 ♪
♪ 当他们逃离你时 ♪
♪ 我内心的恐惧 ♪
♪ 在远处 ♪
♪ 没有转身 ♪
好吧，伙计们。
你确定法律会相信他已经死了？
我是法律，玛丽女士。
如果我说一个人死了，他就死了。
你呢？
你确定这是你想要的？
我一直有点想成为一名副手、警长、元帅。
♪ 拿起打火机过来 ♪
♪ 空气中的火焰，燃烧的小圆面包 ♪
♪ 从山顶呼啸而下 ♪
♪ 告诉他们 说我的爱永不消逝 ♪
你在看什么？
我们有工作要做，爱先生。
呵呵。
我们走吧。
♪ 当我们到达那里时，我们会唱歌 ♪
♪ 摔得越惨 ♪
♪ 跨越天堂爱将响起，响起，响起…… ♪
好的。
♪ 我们该往哪里走？ 我们该跑哪里跑？  ♪
♪ 我们该往哪里走？ 我们该往哪里跑？  ♪
♪ 翻山越岭向阳 ♪
♪ 向着太阳 ♪
♪ 当我们到达那里时，我们会唱歌 ♪
♪ 我们要唱歌 ♪
♪ 穿越天堂爱会响起，响起，响起，响起 ♪
♪ 拿起打火机过来 ♪
♪ 空气中的火焰，燃烧的小圆面包 ♪
♪ 从山顶呼啸而下 ♪
♪ 告诉他们 说我的爱永不消逝 ♪
♪ 我们去哪里？  ♪
♪ 漫长而曲折的道路 ♪
♪ 他们吼得越大声 ♪
♪ 摔得越惨 ♪
- ♪ 看他的圣经和枪 ♪
- ♪ 看他 ♪
♪ Badman 没有scarper nah run ♪
- ♪ 看那个不怕男人的女人 ♪
- ♪ 看她 ♪
- ♪ Bad gyal no Scarper nah run ♪
- ♪ Pam pam ♪
♪ 舔一口 每个人都挥动你的手 ♪
- ♪ de woman jussa 全体起立 ♪
- ♪ 哦，天哪 ♪
- ♪ Bandolero 戴手表当我们走路 ♪
♪ Bad gyal no take bak
no talk 当我说的时候 ♪
♪ 拿起打火机过来 ♪
♪ 空气中的火焰，燃烧的小圆面包 ♪
♪ 从山顶呼啸而下 ♪
♪ 告诉他们 说我的爱永不消逝 ♪
♪ 我们去哪里？  ♪
♪ 漫长而曲折的道路 ♪
♪ 他们吼得越大声 ♪
♪ 摔得越惨 ♪
♪ Fire fi bun Mr Man 我们没时间玩 ♪
♪ 你爱一个女人 日日夜夜告诉她 ♪
♪ 派人过来 知道我马上告诉你 ♪
♪ 我爱你就像我爱我的腰围 ♪
♪ 穿得很漂亮 仍然是我散步 坚韧不拔 ♪
♪ 召集妇女委员会 并骑上他的城市 ♪
♪ 我们两个像鸟一样自由 他们听我的话更好 ♪
♪ 当我说拿起你的打火机过来时 ♪
♪ 空气中的火焰，燃烧的小圆面包 ♪
♪ 从山顶呼啸而下 ♪
♪ 告诉他们说我的爱永不消逝 ♪
♪ 我们去哪里？  ♪
♪ 漫长而曲折的道路 ♪
♪ 他们吼得越大声 ♪
♪ 摔得越惨 ♪
♪ 最好我们跌倒 ♪
♪ 我们的时间是借来的 ♪
♪ 活得像我们的最后一天 ♪
♪ 没有明天 ♪
♪ 我们会重生 ♪
♪ 在一个美丽的早晨 ♪
♪ 像风滚草一样飘扬 ♪
♪ 夜来如贼 ♪
♪ 直到公鸡乌鸦 ♪
♪ 我知道，我知道我们会…… ♪
♪ 拿起打火机过来 ♪
♪ 空气中的火焰，燃烧的小圆面包 ♪
♪ 从山顶呼啸而下 ♪
♪ 告诉他们 说我的爱永不消逝 ♪
♪ 我们去哪里？  ♪
♪ 漫长而曲折的道路 ♪
♪ 他们吼得越大声 ♪
♪ 摔得越惨 ♪
♪ 我们每天都更加努力 ♪
♪ 夜晚，我们活得更快 ♪
♪ 雨越下越大 ♪
♪ 点燃火焰，我们走得更快♪
♪ 对于痛苦会尝试测试我们 ♪
♪ 没有瓦哈拉能打败我们 ♪
♪ 最好知道我们不懒惰 ♪
♪ 最好知道我们会发疯 ♪
♪ 我们每天都更加努力 ♪
♪ 夜晚，我们活得更快 ♪
♪ 雨越下越大 ♪
♪ 点燃火焰，我们走得更快 ♪
♪ 对于痛苦会尝试测试我们 ♪
♪ 没有瓦哈拉能打败我们 ♪
♪ 最好知道我们不懒惰 ♪
♪ 最好知道我们会发疯 ♪
♪ 我们每天都在努力 ♪
♪ 夜晚，我们过得很快 ♪
♪ 当雨下得很大时 ♪
♪ 点燃火焰，我们走得快 ♪
♪ 带他们来，我们走 ♪
♪ 大声一点，安静 不 ♪
♪ 来火，去水 ♪
♪ 唱得更高，别哭了 ♪
♪ 没有人来找我们 我们累了，哦 ♪
♪ 点燃他们看到的火焰 我们更强大，哦 ♪
♪ 我们每天都更加努力 ♪
♪ 夜晚，我们活得更快 ♪
♪ 雨越下越大 ♪
♪ 点燃火焰，我们走得更快 ♪
♪ 对于痛苦会尝试测试我们 ♪
♪ 没有瓦哈拉能打败我们 ♪
♪ 最好知道我们不懒惰 ♪
♪ 最好知道我们会发疯 ♪
♪ 我们每天都更加努力 ♪
♪ 夜晚，我们活得更快 ♪
♪ 雨越下越大 ♪
♪ 点燃火焰，我们走得更快 ♪
♪ 对于痛苦会尝试测试我们 ♪
♪ 没有瓦哈拉能打败我们 ♪
♪ 最好知道我们不懒惰 ♪
♪ 最好知道我们会发疯 ♪
♪ 对于痛苦会尝试测试我们 ♪
♪ 没有瓦哈拉能打败我们 ♪
♪ 最好知道我们不懒惰 ♪
♪ 最好知道我们会发疯 ♪
♪ 我回来时 ♪
♪ 你会看到一个改变的灵魂 ♪
♪ 路太长 ♪
♪ 他们会逃离我 ♪
♪ 当他们逃离你时 ♪
♪ 我内心的恐惧 ♪
♪ 在远处 ♪
♪ 没有转身 ♪
♪ 我走了，对罪人不留情 ♪
♪ 你永远不要转身 ♪
♪ 我来了 ♪
♪ 冬天会痛 ♪
♪ 永远，永远不要发出声音 ♪
♪ 你不要 ♪
♪ 永远，永远 ♪
♪ 发出声音 ♪
♪ 我回来时 ♪
♪ 你会看到一个改变的灵魂 ♪
♪ 路太长 ♪
♪ 他们会逃离我 ♪
♪ 当他们逃离你时 ♪
♪ 我内心的恐惧 ♪
♪ 在远处 ♪
♪ 没有转身 ♪
♪ 不，没有…… ♪